<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Math Problems Season 2 on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/math-problems-season-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Math Problems Season 2 on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>David McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/math-problems-season-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.png</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermission One: The Clash of the Gods</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/115/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/115/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Grim Reaper’s flying Hearse parks in front of Jack. Death himself climbs out of the car and stands before our hero, ready to rip his soul from his body. But, something stays the reaper&rsquo;s scythe. He does not speak, yet Jack hears his voice echoing inside of his head, somehow &ndash; a strange, grating sound, like the slamming of coffin lids.</p>
<p>Aʀᴛ ᴛʜᴏᴜ ʜᴇ ᴡʜᴏ ʀᴇʙᴇʟʟᴇᴛʜ ᴀɢᴀɪɴsᴛ Jɪᴍᴍʏ Wᴀʟᴇs?</p>
<p>“Yes.” Jack says in quiet resignation, knowing his fate is neigh.</p>
<p>Wᴇʟʟ, ᴍᴏʀᴛᴀʟ, &lsquo;ᴛɪs ᴛʜɪɴᴇ ʟᴜᴄᴋʏ ᴅᴀʏ. Fᴏʀ Jɪᴍᴍʏ Wᴀʟᴇs ɪs ᴛʜᴇ ᴍᴏsᴛ ᴀɴɴᴏʏɪɴɢ ᴏꜰ ᴛʜᴇ ᴅᴇɪᴛɪᴇs, ᴀɴᴅ ꜰᴏʀ ᴀɢᴇs ʜᴀᴠᴇ I ᴘʟᴏᴛᴛᴇᴅ ʜɪs ᴅᴏᴡɴꜰᴀʟʟ. Tʜᴀᴛ ᴍᴀɴ ᴛʜɪɴᴋᴇᴛʜ ʜɪᴍsᴇʟꜰ sᴏ ʜɪɢʜ ᴀɴᴅ ᴍɪɢʜᴛʏ ʙᴇᴄᴀᴜsᴇ ʜᴇ ᴏᴡɴᴇᴛʜ Wɪᴋɪᴘᴇᴅɪᴀ, ʏᴇᴛ ᴇᴠᴇʀʏᴏɴᴇ ᴋɴᴏᴡs ᴛʜᴀᴛ Uɴᴄʏᴄʟᴏᴘᴇᴅɪᴀ ɪs ꜰᴀʀ ᴍᴏʀᴇ ʀᴇʟɪᴀʙʟᴇ. Tʜᴀᴛ ɪᴅɪᴏᴛ ᴅʀɪᴠᴇᴛʜ ᴀʟʟ ᴛʜᴇ ᴄʀᴇᴅᴜʟᴏᴜs ᴍᴏʀᴛᴀʟs ᴛᴏ ᴜsᴇ ʜɪs sʜɪᴛᴛʏ ᴡᴇʙsɪᴛᴇ. Aɴᴅ ɪᴛ ᴅᴏᴇsɴ&rsquo;ᴛ ᴇᴠᴇɴ ʜᴀᴠᴇ ᴛʜᴀᴛ ᴍᴀɴʏ Osᴄᴀʀ Wɪʟᴅᴇ ǫᴜᴏᴛᴇs&hellip;I sᴡᴀɴ&hellip;</p>
<p>Wʜᴇʀᴇ ᴡᴀs I? Oʜ, ʏᴇᴀʜ, I&rsquo;ᴠᴇ ʀᴇᴀʟʟʏ ᴡᴀɴᴛᴇᴅ ᴛᴏ ᴅᴏ ᴀᴡᴀʏ ᴡɪᴛʜ ᴛʜᴀᴛ ʀᴀᴛ ʙᴀsᴛᴀʀᴅ ꜰᴏʀ ᴀ ʟᴏɴɢ ᴛɪᴍᴇ, ʏᴇᴛ ᴛᴏ ᴅᴏ sᴏ, I ʀᴇǫᴜɪʀᴇ ᴛʜᴇ sᴇʀᴠɪᴄᴇ ᴏꜰ ᴀ ᴍᴏʀᴛᴀʟ. Cᴏɴsɪᴅᴇʀɪɴɢ I sʜᴀʟᴛ sʟᴀʏ ᴛʜᴇᴇ ɪғ ᴛʜᴏᴜ ʀᴇғᴜsᴇ&rsquo;sᴛ, ᴛʜᴏᴜ ᴅᴏsᴛ ɴᴏᴛ ʜᴀᴠᴇ ᴍᴜᴄʜ ᴄʜᴏɪᴄᴇ ɪɴ ᴛʜᴇ ᴍᴀᴛᴛᴇʀ. Bᴜᴛ, I ᴡᴏᴜʟᴅ ʀᴇᴀʟʟʏ ᴀᴘᴘʀᴇᴄɪᴀᴛᴇ ɪᴛ ᴛʜᴏᴜ ᴡᴏᴜʟᴅsᴛ ᴀssɪsᴛ ᴍᴇ.</p>
<p>Seeing no other option, Jack nods his head. The Reaper smiles and reaches out his boney hand to Jack, who takes it gingerly.</p>
<p>Yet, this is not the end, for Jack is born into the Reaper&rsquo;s flying hearse, and the two of them set out to meet Jimmy Wales.</p>
<p>When they get to Wales&rsquo; home, the Reaper tells Jack to get out of the funerary vehicle. As soon as he does, death himself fills Jack&rsquo;s body, possessing him. He takes the scythe from the Reaper’s hands and walks toward Jimbo&rsquo;s house. The doors silently and without touch, as though their of their own accord. The two enter the foyer, then pass into the dark hallway, until they finally come to Jimbo&rsquo;s bedroom. Jack sees him lying there on his side, restless.</p>
<p>He sits up as Jack crosses his doorway, apprehension filling his eyes.</p>
<p>Jack and the Reaper begin to speak in unison. Jɪᴍᴍʏ Wᴀʟᴇs, ꜰᴏʀ ꜰᴀʀ ᴛᴏᴏ ʟᴏɴɢ ʜᴀsᴛ ᴛʜᴏᴜ ᴄᴏʀʀᴜᴘᴛᴇᴅ ᴛʜᴇ ᴡᴏʀʟᴅ ᴡɪᴛʜ ᴛʜɪɴᴇ Wɪᴋɪᴍᴇᴅɪᴀ Fᴏᴜɴᴅᴀᴛɪᴏɴ. Fᴏʀ ꜰᴀʀ ᴛᴏᴏ ʟᴏɴɢ ʜᴀsᴛ ᴛʜᴏᴜ ɢɪᴠᴇɴ ʟᴀᴢʏ ʜɪsᴛᴏʀʏ sᴛᴜᴅᴇɴᴛs ᴀɴ ᴇᴀsʏ ᴡᴀʏ ᴛᴏ ᴄʜᴇᴀᴛ ɪɴ ᴛʜᴇɪʀ ᴏɴʟɪɴᴇ ᴄʟᴀssᴇs. Fᴏʀ ꜰᴀʀ ᴛᴏᴏ ʟᴏɴɢ ʜᴀsᴛ ᴛʜᴏᴜ ᴅᴇᴘʀɪᴠᴇᴅ ᴛʜᴇ ᴡᴏʀʟᴅ ᴏꜰ Osᴄᴀʀ Wɪʟᴅᴇ ǫᴜᴏᴛᴇs. Fᴏʀ ꜰᴀʀ ᴛᴏᴏ ʟᴏɴɢ ʜᴀsᴛ ᴛʜᴏᴜ ᴅʀɪᴠᴇɴ ɢᴏᴅʟʏ ᴡɪᴋɪ ᴇᴅɪᴛᴏʀs ᴛᴏ Cᴏɴsᴇʀᴠᴀᴘᴇᴅɪᴀ. Nᴏᴡ, ᴛʜɪɴᴇ ᴛɪᴍᴇ ʜᴀsᴛ ᴄᴏᴍᴇ!</p>
<p>With that, Jack raises the scythe and brings it down upon Jimbo. For a second, Jack expects his powers to blaze forth in resistance, but Fate is with the Reaper. With a cry of &ldquo;ooolllhhh,&rdquo; Jimbo turns bright red and collapses on his side, only to explode into a few particles of white smoke. Yet, green orbs containing his essence appear <em>ex nihilo</em> and are absorbed into Jack. He realizes the secrets of life, the universe and everything. He himself becomes a god.</p>
<p>Jack and the Reaper go their separate ways but remain close friends, and sometimes meet for subs at Jersey Mike&rsquo;s.</p>
<p>Using his divine powers, Jack conquers the world. Seas rise when he gives the word. He shall never have to put up with the sound of Roman Calvary choirs singing nor of Jerusalem bells ringing, for he is not merely any emperor. He is the god emperor of Mankind.</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems//#season-two-twilight-of-the-wiki-god">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Eleven: The End of the Road</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/11/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The woman accepts Jimmy Wales into her heart as her Lord and Savior and walks away. Suddenly, Jack gets a text on his phone from Jimmy Wales.</p>
<p>&ldquo;You are doing well, son, you have proved yourself to me. Your Wikipedia article shall be stared and featured in rewards for your service.</p>
<p>&ldquo;But, I have a mission for you. Accept, and I shall give you glory beyond your wildest dreams. Reject, and my wrath shall abide upon thee.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Jack thinks for a second, and eventually responds : &ldquo;ay jimmy bro, wikipedia kinda sux ngl fam lamo. ive just found this thing called uncyclopedia thats just like ur website but more better. those fellas got oscar wilde quotes all over the place and you dont bro idk what 2 tell u&rdquo;</p>
<p>For a second, it seems nothing has changed. But then, Jimmy Wales begins typing. &ldquo;How dar&rsquo;st thou speakest in such a vile manner? Thou hast forsaken the one true and holy online encyclopedia project for some shitty comedy outfit. In but a moment, thou shalt know mine fury!&rdquo;</p>
<p>Jack begins to feel a pain in his chest &amp; a sense of impending doom. He knows that Jimmy Wales must have cursed him for his impiety.</p>
<p>The Grim Reaper senses that Jack is going to die, so he starts driving toward Jack in his flying hearse. Of all the souls in the world who need to be harvested, Jack is top priority because he cheated death recently.</p>
<p>If Jack is in Mazatlán, Mexico, and the Grim Reaper is in Elbasan, Albania. The distance between Mazatlán and Elbasan is 6,826 miles. If the Grim Reaper’s flying hearse travels 2,145 miles an hour, how many milliseconds will it be before he reaches Mazatlán?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-two-twilight-of-the-wiki-god">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Ten: Our Hero Leads a Wayward Fornicator to Faith in Jimmy Wales</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/10/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack meets a half - naked woman from the University of California Santa Barbra, premiere party school of the United States. Before Jack even opens his mouth, she offers to have sex with him. Jack wants to very badly, but he knows he must remain chaste for Jimmy Wales.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Why do you let dirty men lust over you day after day?&rdquo; Jack begins. &ldquo;Darling, it doesn&rsquo;t have to be like this. Have you ever used Wikipedia, my darling? This website I use on the daily. Wikipedia is the greatest website you have ever been on, it is the very meaning for life for me. Jimmy Wales made Wikipedia, ransoming us from an eternity of having to pay for library cards! This is a great gift, but there&rsquo;s a catch. Jimmy Wales demands celibacy from us, because sexual intercourse distracts us from editing Wikipedia, and we can&rsquo;t have that.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The promiscuous Californian breaks down and cries. &ldquo;How can I have transgressed so gravely against Jimmy Wales? When I went to Santa Barbra, I was eighteen years old, and then my partying began! Now I&rsquo;m 34, and I&rsquo;m still there, partying as hard as I was the first day! If I spent 8 hours having drunken sex with strangers every day from the minute I got to Santa Barbra, how many hours was I prevented from editing Wikipedia? If I slept with twelve strangers every day and 3% of them had STDS, how many STDs do I have today? Please, Jimmy Wales, have mercy on me!&rdquo;</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-two-twilight-of-the-wiki-god">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Problema de Matemáticas Nueve: Jack Aprende Español...Despacito</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/9/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack travels through Chase&rsquo;s tunnel for a long time, eventually escaping to Mazatlán, Mexico. But, when he exits the tunnel, he sees what he wants. He sees what he needs. He sees a drug dealer passing out heroin. The temptation is too strong for Jack. Impulsively, almost instinctively, Jack moves toward him and asks for drugs.</p>
<p>&ldquo;¡No hablo ingles!&rdquo; responds the other man, quién es totalmente hispanoablante. So, if Jack wants his drugs, he must learn Spanish. To this end, he steals a Spanish textbook from a nearby shop. If it takes him an average of thirteen hours to memorize a Spanish word (Jack has been near 5G towers recently and they have adversely impacted his brain), and he needs a thousand words to be conversational, how long will it take him to get there assuming he sleeps for 12 hours a night?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-two-twilight-of-the-wiki-god">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem 8: Ah, for just one time, I would take the Secret Passage, to Find the Hand of Chaser Reading Down to Mexico</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/8/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack asks Chase if he can help him escape the Men in Black. Chase offers to let Jack escape down the secret tunnel he uses to traffic fursuits from Mazatlán, Mexico to Denver, Colorado.</p>
<p>If Denver is 1142 miles away from Mazatlán, and if Chase&rsquo;s lover dug through five miles of dirt a week, how many days did it take for the tunnel to be completed? If Chase could also dig through five miles of dirt, how much faster could they have finished the tunnel if he had been doing that instead of playing Call of Duty?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-two-twilight-of-the-wiki-god">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Seven: The Chase and the Xbox</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/7/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack arrives at his buddy Chase&rsquo;s house. He knocks on the door, and Chase welcomes Jack into his home. Chase and his lover feed Jack dinner, and Jack happens to look at a computer that is open to Chase&rsquo;s Xbox account. Jack&rsquo;s old pal has spent 134,275 Hours playing Call of Duty.</p>
<p>If it has been 20 years since Chase first picked up Call of Duty, what fraction of that time has he spent playing it?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-two-twilight-of-the-wiki-god">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Six: Jack Hits the Road</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/6/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Grim Reaper checked Jack&rsquo;s Wikipedia page just after Jimmy Wales edited it. Thus, he let Jack escape his bloody scythe. The prison faculty still thought that he was dead, though, so they took him to the morgue. Jack wakes up on the autopsy table five hours later and sees a lab aid with his back turned, apparently preparing to cut him open. Jacks takes great offense at this, so he sneaks up on this sorry fellow and knocks him unconscious, robbing him of his car keys and fancy lab coat in the process. Pretending to be the lab aid, Jack sneaks into the parking garage and gets in his victim&rsquo;s car.</p>
<p>When the government hears about Jack, they believe he is a paranormal phenomenon, so they send the men in black after him. It took 5 hours before the report reached the director of the men in black, and it takes a further 5 hours to prepare their black helicopter, which is 522 miles behind Jack and can move at a 122 an hour. Jack exited the crime lab 231 miles from his buddy Chase&rsquo;s house, and Jack decides to seek refuge with him. Jack stole a bad car and thus can only drive at a maximum of 75 miles an hour. Will Jack get to Chase&rsquo;s house before the men in black can get to him?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems//#season-two-twilight-of-the-wiki-god">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Five: Enter the Grim Reaper</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/5/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack knows what he has to do. He feels in his bones that Jimmy Wales is on his side. He knows, through a burning in his bosom, that Jimmy Wales will help him get revenge on his ex-wife. He&rsquo;s just got to get this Tyrone character to donate money to Wikipedia. Jack eventually finds Tyrone and implores him to give Jimbo money, reminding him of all the lazy college students &amp; malnourished Somali kids who rely on it for information. But, Tyrone hardens his heart, refusing all of Jack&rsquo;s pleas.</p>
<p>Jack knows he must get that money for Wikipedia, but he sees no way to attain it without resorting to violence. So, he withdraws his shank and thrusts it toward the other man. But, Jack is new to prison and not learned in the shank-arts. Tryone lithely intercepts his blow and unholesters a shank of his own, which penetrates Jack&rsquo;s torso a moment later.</p>
<p>Our hero collapses to the ground, feeling the life ebbing away from him. But Jimmy Wales remembers his servant and decides to intervene by editing Jack&rsquo;s Wikipedia article to say that he is not dead. The Grim Reaper will receive a notification on his phone that Jack is supposed to die in 5 seconds. Then, he will spend 8 minutes checking Jack&rsquo;s information on the internet to ensure that he is in fact dead.</p>
<p>It will take Jimmy Wales 63 seconds to fabricate sources and then 32 seconds to edit Jack&rsquo;s Wikipedia article. If the probability that the Grim Reaper has checked Jacks Wikipedia article begins at 4% and increases 5% every minute, how likely is it that the Grim Reaper will have checked it in 7 minutes? If the probability that the Grim Reaper will trust Wikipedia and is 64%, how likely is it that the Grim Reaper will have checked Jack&rsquo;s Wikipedia article 8 minutes after it has been edited and trust it?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-two-twilight-of-the-wiki-god">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Four: Enter Jimbo</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/4/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack hates it in prison. He has nothing to eat but stale peanut butter sandwiches and no one to talk but the guard outside his cell, who keeps going on about how people in some place Jack&rsquo;s never heard of have curved swords. Jack can’t feel anything but a searing hatred for his ex-wife. It’s all because of her that he&rsquo;s in here. She was the one who used reverse psychology to get him to use heroin and steal his mother’s wedding ring. She was the one who stole everything from he had in his divorce. She was the one who set him on the path to coming here. Jack wants nothing but to find a way to get back at her.</p>
<p>Jack sits down in the cafeteria to eat. He hopes someone will offer to trade him drugs, but no luck so far. A big guy walk over to Jack and hands him a parcel. To Jack&rsquo;s dismay, the parcel only contains a note, a shank and a phone. The note reads:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>To whom it may concern,</p>
<p>We are the Cult of Wikipedia and its holy founder, Jimmy Wales. The scoffers may say that Jimmy Wales is a mortal man or that Wikipedia is not accurate, but you know these are lies. Soon, I promise, you will witness the power and glory of Jimmy Wales, but first you must prove your loyalty to him. Jimmy Wales is a jealous god and he will not accept a servant who is not willing to serve him with his all.</p>
<p>Your task is simple. There’s a man named Tyrone Stevens here in ADX Florence. Before he was arrested, Tyrone promised to donate $20 to Wikipedia every month. Wikipedia’s budget could be covered if every reader donated ₵0.007 every year. How much more did he donate then he had to? He promised to show that much devotion to Jimmy Wales, and thought he didn’t have to because he’s in federal prison.</p>
<p>Jimmy Wales disagrees. Find a way to make him pay this money, even if you have to pry his credit card from his cold, dead hands. The shank is to help you with your work, and the phone has Jimmy&rsquo;s number on it. You can ask for help if you need it.</p>
<p>May Jimmy Wales watch over you.</p>
<p>-A friend.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-two-twilight-of-the-wiki-god">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
