<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Math Problems Season 5 on AlvinMcGee.xyz</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/math-problems-season-5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Math Problems Season 5 on AlvinMcGee.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Alvin McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/math-problems-season-5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.svg</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Epilogue: The Eschatological Victory of Jack</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/epilogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/epilogue/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Though the antichrist was able to render Jack unconscious and cast him into a coma, Pastor Jim and his armada of Florida men were able to prevail over the beast in the end. Having been defeated, Chase returned to Heck. But this time, as he had been the antichrist, he was numbered among the worst and gravest of sinners; leading to his imprisonment in the deepest and darkest pit of Heck. But, as our heroes learned earlier, it is the most sublime, pleasant, and sexually stimulating of them all. So, all things considered, this was a win for him.</p>
<p>Our heroes (except for Jack, who was still in a coma) found themselves in a world in which, though not completely marred by the archons, had still been afflicted by them. So, Philip lead the push to renew the world.</p>
<p>Just as through one man, the antichrist, all were to be made cringe, so through one man, Philip, all were made based. Just as through one man the many would be made soyjacks, so through one man the many were made chads. But each in its own order: Philip, the firstfruits, and then those like Philip on his arrival. Then came the end, when he destroyed every archon and authority and power. (The last enemy to be destroyed was the IRS) Then, when Philip had put all things in subjection under his feet, he subjected himself to Jack, so that Jack might be all in all.</p>
<p>In Kingdom of Jack, all influence of the archons has been expunged. As Pastor Jim foretold long ages ago, fast food restaurants other than Chick-fil-a have been abolished - never again will anyone get fries and a drink without being wished a blessed day. Mandatory vaccinations have been replaced with injections of various veterinary medicines, and breatharianism is now accepted nutritional orthodoxy. The gays have been returned to the closet, and the only legal use of the word &ldquo;gay&rdquo; is as a schoolyard insult. Everyone has admitted what they all knew from looking at the trees all along: that there is no God but God and Pastor Jim is his messenger. At Pastor Jim&rsquo;s bidding, Creationism has been returned to public schools. Indeed, all teaching of mainstream science has been outlawed, and science curricula are now solely based on Kent Hovind lectures. Nevermore will anyone see violence in movies nor sex on TV. Yea verily, sex has been abolished. The moon landing has been revealed as the farce it always was, and everyone knows about Agartha. The truth about 9/11 (whatever it is) has finally come out. The birth control, estrogen, micro-plastics, and fluoride that the archons put in the drinking water has been replaced with Nugenix Total-T testosterone booster, which has made all fricking frogs straight.</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-five-parousia">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Forty: It&#39;s the End of the Line of the Final Journey</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/40/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/40/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack and his friends run into Jeffery Epstein&rsquo;s house, frantically searching for George Soros and Klaus Schwab - the last two of the archons.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Wait,&rdquo; says Philip, &ldquo;I hear them on the balcony upstairs, the one overlooking the ocean! They&rsquo;re talking in Latin, must be summoning the antichrist right now.&rdquo;</p>
<p>They rush up the stairs like there&rsquo;s no tomorrow. With the power of four demigods, Shaggy, Philip, Jack, and Jimmy Wales burst through the door out onto the balcony. They see Klaus Schwab and George Soros standing over a pentagram in goofy black robes.</p>
<p>Klaus Schwab turns towards them, and he begins to cackle maniacally. &ldquo;You are too late! Ze ritual is completed.&rdquo; He turns toward the ocean. &ldquo;Rise! Rise my precious!&rdquo;</p>
<p>With horror, Jack gazes over the railing. And lo, he sees a beast rising out of the sea, and out of its mouth pour words of blasphemy  (or maybe they&rsquo;re racial slurs, he isn&rsquo;t really sure). It is a huge, humanoid fox with blue fur. It at least a hundred feet tall, clothed in nothing but a fedora atop its head and an <em>Angels and Airwaves</em> hoodie upon its back.</p>
<p>It turns towards them, and Jack is horrified by what he sees. &ldquo;You dirty pilgrims!&rdquo; the beast bellows. &ldquo;You found my ass in Heck, but you left me there because that sandwich huffin&rsquo; Jewish piece of shit don&rsquo;t like the things I say about his race!&rdquo;</p>
<p>Cold, hard realization comes over Jack. &ldquo;Chase?&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;You bundle of sticks, I was once Chase, but now I&rsquo;ve been reborn as the damn antichirst! I&rsquo;m gonna rule the whole damn world! But first, I gotta deal with you. You and that sandwich - gobbling Jew!&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Like, zoinks!&rdquo; yells Shaggy, trying to flee in panic.</p>
<p>But, Chase raises his right hand, and his psychic powers blaze forth. Slightly lewd furry art fills minds of his foes - making them fall to their knees in pain. Chase wades towards them, preparing to strike.</p>
<p>&ldquo;So this is how it ends,&rdquo; Jack says. &ldquo;I&rsquo;ve done all this toil, gone on this journey through death and Hades, and it was all for naught. The antichrist is here, and there&rsquo;s nothing we can do to oppose him. He&rsquo;ll conquer the world and destroy liberty. He&rsquo;ll make eating raw meat and taking horse dewormer a thing of the past.</p>
<p>&ldquo;But still,&rdquo; he says on a more somber note, &ldquo;I&rsquo;m glad that you are here with me, Shaggy, here at the end of all things.&rdquo;
&ldquo;Like &hellip; zoinks?&rdquo; Shaggy responds weakly, collapsing from exhaustion immediately after.</p>
<p>But, just as all hope is lost, Jack sees something out of the corner of his eye.</p>
<p>Behind Chase, there is a veritable armada of Florida men, and at their head stands Pastor Jim, King James Bible in hand, ready to do combat. They have come on their pet gators, their boogie boards, and their nuclear powered house boats; armed with their beer, their mosquito nets, and their squirt guns filled with piss.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Light him up, boys!&rdquo; screams Pastor Jim, and the armada and the beast begin their duel. Jack wants to join them in fighting the good fight, but he feels himself loosing consciousness, the furries of Chase are simply too much.</p>
<hr>
<p>If there are 22,244,823 people in Florida and roughly half of these are men, how many are Florida men? If about an eighth of these have come to do battle with the antichrist, how many of them are there?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems#season-five-parousia">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Nine: Cornpop is a Bad Dude</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/39/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/39/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack and his crew steal Elon Musk&rsquo;s fastest UFO and return once more to the Earth. They land on Jeffery Epstein&rsquo;s island - now restored to its previous glory - to find Joe Biden and Bill Clinton standing in front of the door.</p>
<p>&ldquo;What the hell kid?&rdquo; asks Bill Clinton. &ldquo;I thought you died!&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;I was once slain, but now I live. I am Jack, conqueror of death!&rdquo;</p>
<p>Bill is about to respond, but he&rsquo;s cut off by the other archon.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Shabapaduba?&rdquo; Joe Biden questions, gesturing vaguely towards Kaegan with a befuddled expression on his face. &ldquo;I-I coulda sworn, man. That right there is Corn Pop! He&rsquo;s a bad dude, usedta run a buncha bad boys&hellip;&rdquo;</p>
<p>Kaegan throws up his hands. &ldquo;I don&rsquo;t know bro. I ain&rsquo;t named Corn Pop. There are 8 billion people in the world and only one corn pop. I probably ain&rsquo;t him.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Biden grows angry and begins foaming at the mouth. &ldquo;Come on man! You ain&rsquo;t black, you lying, dog - faced pony soldier! You&rsquo;re a Corn Pop &lsquo;cause I says you&rsquo;re a Corn Pop!&rdquo; The politician throws his head back in anger and thrusts forwards his right hand. &ldquo;BIDEN BLAST!&rdquo; he screams in fury, causing a blue pulse of energy to arc between his hand and Kaegan, - reducing the later to a pile of ashes.</p>
<p>&ldquo;No!&rdquo; Screams Hayden. &ldquo;They killed Kaegan!&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;You bastards!&rdquo; I echo.</p>
<p>Fury begins rising in Jack&rsquo;s bosom, fury like he&rsquo;s never felt before. His eyes glow red with wrath - the wrath of the god emperor of mankind. The Earth begins to shake and thunder roles. &ldquo;Lɪsᴛᴇɴ ᴜᴘ, sᴏᴄɪᴀʟɪsᴛ sᴄᴜᴍ!&rdquo; outpours an otherworldly, ferocious voice quite unlike his own. &ldquo;Yᴏᴜ&rsquo;ᴠᴇ ᴋɪʟʟᴇᴅ Kᴇᴀɢᴀɴ, ʙᴜᴛ ʜᴇ ᴡᴀsɴ&rsquo;ᴛ ᴛʜᴇ ꜰɪʀsᴛ! I ᴋɴᴏᴡ ᴛʜᴇ ʜɪsᴛᴏʀʏ ᴏꜰ ʏᴏᴜʀ sᴏᴄɪᴀʟɪsᴍ! I ᴋɴᴏᴡ ᴛʜᴇ ᴡᴏʀᴅs ʏᴏᴜ ᴄᴀɴ&rsquo;ᴛ sᴛᴀɴᴅ ᴛᴏ ʜᴇᴀʀ, ᴛʜᴇ ᴡᴏʀᴅs ᴛʜᴀᴛ ᴇxᴏʀᴄɪsᴇ ᴀɴʏ ʟɪʙᴇʀᴀʟ ғʀᴏᴍ ᴛʜɪs ᴍᴏʀᴛᴀʟ ᴘʟᴀɴᴇ!</p>
<p><em><strong>&ldquo;ɪPʜᴏɴᴇ! &hellip;</strong></em></p>
<p><em><strong>&hellip; Vᴇɴᴇᴢᴜᴇʟᴀ! &hellip;</strong></em></p>
<p><em><strong>&hellip; ONE HUNDRED &hellip;</strong></em></p>
<p><em><strong>&hellip; UNDECILLION &hellip;</strong></em></p>
<p><em><strong>&hellip; DDDEEEAAADDD!!!!&rdquo;</strong></em></p>
<p>The fiends cover their ears, trying to shield themselves from those fateful, ruinous words. But, it is to no avail. They begin screeching in pain, and soon are melting away like the Nazis at the end of <em>Indiana Jones and the Raiders of the Lost Ark.</em></p>
<p>Jack sighs. &ldquo;Another cuck leftist destroyed.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&hellip;</p>
<p>If socialism killed 100 undecillion people, as Jack proved with facts and logic, and there are 8 billion people in the world right now (as Kaegan stated), then how many orders of magnitude more people has socialism killed then are alive today?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-five-parousia">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Eight: Tesla Man - Least of the Archons</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/38/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/38/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>At the crack of Philip&rsquo;s whip, Star in the Morning Sky begins lumbering forwards on her borderline defunct legs. As she reaches 8.8 miles per hour, Jack and his company enter the tunnel of light once more. As they go forward, Jack ceases to be the disembodied ghost he has been, and finds himself arrayed as the god - emperor of mankind once more. His triceps swell, he gains the abs of an anime tomboy, and golden armor covers his body.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Wait, something&rsquo;s wrong!&rdquo; Philip declares with manly yet apprehensive perturbance. &ldquo;Earth isn&rsquo;t up ahead! This darned horse is taking us to the moon!&rdquo;</p>
<p>But, before Philip can stop anything, the tunnel of light vanishes, and the carriage grinds to a halt on solid, firmly material ground. Jack closes his eyes, expecting to die like an imposter thrown out of the airlock. But, he doesn&rsquo;t. He breathes in and slowly opens his eyes, finding himself still very much alive.</p>
<p>They step outside the carriage to find themselves in a hideous moon base, made entirely of plastic - exactly like every generic spaceship on TV.</p>
<p>&ldquo;What the hell is going on! Wikipedia doesn&rsquo;t say anything about there being a base like this on the moon!&rdquo; says Jimmy Wales.</p>
<p>A strange, A.I. generated cackling sounds behind them. &ldquo;Ha. Ha. Ha. You are fools.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Jack turns around wildly and draws his sword, but he only sees an expensive - looking Tesla car. But then, its parts begin shifting into a new form - the form of a huge man made of plastic and steel.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Like zoinks! It&rsquo;s a transformer!&rdquo; Shaggy proclaims.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Before my augmentation, I was called Elon Musk, and I am the least of the archons. How dare you trespass on my moon base?&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Wait, this is totally fake!&rdquo; I say. &ldquo;How come no one found this place when people went to the moon? There has to be a naturalistic explanation for this.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;No, no one ever went to the moon. This is where UFOs hail from, and it has been so since the time of the ancient Egyptians. To keep the mortals from discovering them, they were forbidden from coming to the moon.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Just as I am about to respond, Jimmy Wales jumps into action and begins doing battle with Elon Musk - quoting negative statistics about spaceX and Tesla all the while. The fight is long, hard, and brutal. But, in the end, the African American businessman falls to his knees in subjection.</p>
<p>&ldquo;No! You may have defeated me, but you cannot defeat the other archons! You are on the road to destruction! All of your base are belong to us! The others are gathered at Jeffry Epstein&rsquo;s island, and they will summon the antichrist in 37 minutes, bringing about the end times. My fastest UFO will get you there in 27 minutes. How long, pray tell, will that leave you to fight them?&rdquo;</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-five-parousia">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
