<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Math Problems Season 4 on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/math-problems-season-4/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Math Problems Season 4 on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>David McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/math-problems-season-4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.png</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Seven: Look, Ma, I no Fourth Wall!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/37/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/37/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack and his compatriots steel themselves for what&rsquo;s ahead: the deepest pit of Heck, where the worst and gravest of sinners are eternally tortured. The place from whence Jack must rescue a soul to aid him in his quest.</p>
<p>But, when they get there, they&rsquo;re pleasantly surprised. It just looks like a bar. Some lit EDM beats are playing in the background. The stench of beer can be detected everywhere. And &hellip;</p>
<p><em>Oh.</em></p>
<p>There are many sensuous, scantily - clad succubi gyrating atop the tables. It&rsquo;s not just a bar, it&rsquo;s a strip club!</p>
<p>&ldquo;Woah.&rdquo; says Keagan. &ldquo;I&rsquo;m not normally down bad for the forces of darkness, but I am a man &hellip;&rdquo;</p>
<p>Jack sees two people he knew in life: Jimmy Wales and his old pal David McGee. Both of them are sitting at a table, ogling a particularly voluptuous succubus with short brown hair.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Yo, Dave, Jimmy, why is this circle of Heck so fun? Isn&rsquo;t it supposed to be like for the worst of the worst?&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Oh, hey Jack,&rsquo; I say, taking my eyes of off my favored succubus for a second. &ldquo;Well, this circle of Heck sucked for a long time. The archangel Samael was ordered to torture truly grave sinners. But, Sammael had a soft heart, and he couldn&rsquo;t find it within himself to devise horrific tortures. But, after Uriel loaned him <em>The Apocalypse of Peter</em> and the Quran, he realized that humans were far more sadistic than he was, so he decided to base this circle on human depictions of Heck.</p>
<p>This was a really good bet for a long time &ndash; it used to be horrible here! People were eternally forced to drink boiling water, guys were hung from the roof by their testicles, little children were trapped in scorching ovens, there was something about a girl being painted blue &hellip; [1]</p>
<p>&ldquo;But, then the Enlightenment happened, and more people began to realize all this was evil balderdash, so Heck needed a makeover in the popular imagination. C.S. Lewis was up for the job, and he claimed that Heck was just voluntary separation from God. He published a book about this in 1945, and it became quite popular. This became the dominant picture of Heck in 10% of churches per decade. And, when they became a majority, the only thing keeping people here was their own free will.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Fortunately, that meant old Sammie needed to invent a reason for people to stay! What kind of idiot would just stay in Heck for the Heck of it? So, after sleeping on it, good angel hired some succubi to make this circle more appealing. After all, everyone in Heck is down bad and there ain&rsquo;t no sex in Heaven. All of the men happily took Samael up on his offer, but many of the women only agreed after considerable pleading and conversion therapy.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Philip, calculate what year that happened!&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Wait, before I have to do the math on that,&rdquo; begins Philip, who apparently became rather knowledgable about theology while in Limbo, &ldquo;how do Christians who believe in annihilationism or purgatorial universalism, like Arnobius and St. Gregory of Nyssa, fit into this calculation of yours?&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;See,&rdquo; I respond, &ldquo;it&rsquo;s not about what theology people hold, it&rsquo;s about how Heck is described in popular culture. If <em>Lilith</em> became as popular as <em>The Great Divorce,</em> this party would come to a screeching halt.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Oh okay,&rdquo; Jack says, &ldquo;but I gotta ask, why are you here and how&rsquo;d you get here? I know Jimmy was a terrible person and I beat the snot out of him. But Dave, you&rsquo;re just a normal guy who writes stupid jokes, thinks Heroes 4 is a decent game, and occasionally looks at women with lust in his heart. What did you do to deserve this?&rdquo; Suddenly, he gasps with horror, &ldquo;You didn&rsquo;t become an NIMBY, did you!?&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;No, no! Not even I could sink to that level of depravity!&rdquo; I respond. &ldquo;It all started when I stopped sending Hayden superchats and supporting him on OnlyFans. He didn&rsquo;t take to that very nicely and threw me into a meat grinder. But that didn&rsquo;t actually kill me. I only died because, when Philip got into a car crash, a beer bottle flew out of his hand and through his open window, eventually making contact with my head and killing me instantly. Thankfully, the night before that, I&rsquo;d joined Pastor Jim&rsquo;s Bible Church of East Pensacola. So, I got saved! But, they ain&rsquo;t got no sex in Heaven, and they do have it down here. So, I occasionally mosey on down to the low places for a little, uh, bling bling.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Oh&hellip;okay&hellip;&rdquo; responds Jack, wishing he hadn&rsquo;t asked. &ldquo;Well, either way, I&rsquo;m getting a burning in my bosom which is telling me that Jimmy Wales is the guy I was supposed to save from Heck for my quest, so he&rsquo;s coming with us. You wanna come, Dave?&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Yeah, sure. They probably have sex in the mortal realm too.&rdquo;</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
<hr>
<p>[1] Save the last one, which is of course a reference none of you will get, all of these are lifted from real depictions of Hell. Respectively, they come from Surah 22:19 - 22, the Apocalypse of Peter, and John Furniss&rsquo; pamphlet, &ldquo;The Sight of Hell.&rdquo;</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermission 3: A Cat that Really is Gone</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/37-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/37-5/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack and his friends now come to Satan’s throne room in the city of Pandaleerium, which was built to guard the gates of Heck against darned souls seeking to escape. But, Satan’s throne is empty. Beside it stands the goat demon Baphomet, who looks rather tired.</p>
<p>“What happened to Satan, man? I was looking forward to whipping his ass!” says Philip.</p>
<p>Baphomet sighs. “Well, see, the left is right, Satan is actually Donald Trump. Since all of us demons are Democrats, we got a bit perturbed when he decided to run as a Republican, but at first it wasn&rsquo;t anything serious. Then, Beelzebub decided to get us Twitter and cable news down here, and we truly learned the depths of his depravity. As his drinking and lusting and his hunger for power became known to more and more demons, the demands to do something about this outrageous man grew louder and louder. So, eventually, we threw him out.”</p>
<p>“Oh, so like, are you going to do anything to stop us from leaving Heck?”</p>
<p>“Nah, we’re too tired. There ain&rsquo;t no coffee in Heck. There’s a carriage over there which will take you back to the mortal world. It’s pulled by a haggard, undead mare named Star in the Morning Sky (cause horse owners name their animals horrible names like that).”</p>
<p>So, Jack and his friends pile into the carriage and return to the mortal world and do battle with the archons.</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Six: Two True Scotsmen</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/36/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/36/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The next circle of Heck looks rather peaceful. When Jack first enters it, nothing seems out of the ordinary. He can hear nothing but the soft, quiet breeze, though a part of him thinks someone is humming &ldquo;The Wheels on the Bus.&rdquo; All he sees is a pot roasting over a campfire, about which two people are sitting quietly. After a moment, he recognizes them as Shrek and John Duns Scotus.</p>
<p>&lsquo;Like zoinks!&quot; exclaims Shaggy. &ldquo;Shrek, I was your biggest fan! John Duns Scotus, you were incredibly influential on my understanding of the univocity of theological verbiage! What did you guys do to, like, get darned to Heck!?!?!&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Ah, I&rsquo;m happy to have shaped ya intellectual formation, laddie!&rdquo; says John Duns Scotus. &ldquo;But it ain&rsquo;t us who got our arses darned to Heck.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;No laddie,&rdquo; says Shrek, &ldquo;we&rsquo;re <em>true</em> Scotsmen, and the Scots are God&rsquo;s holy and chosen people. So we got saved despite not being part of Pastor Jim&rsquo;s Bible Church of East Pensacola.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;But, aren&rsquo;t there like, plenty of Scotsmen who get darned to Heck though?&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;No <em>true</em> Scot would ever do such a thing!&rdquo; declares John Duns Scotus. &ldquo;He may wear his kilt and read his Glasgow Morning Herald, but he isn&rsquo;t a <em>true</em> Scotsmen! We are the sole <em>true</em> Scotsmen in history (George MacDonald almost made the cut, but he was far too reasonable for Pastor Jim&rsquo;s liking). If only two Scotsmen in the history of Scotland were true Scotsmen, and there have been around 700 million Scotsmen in history, what percentage of Scotsmen are truly Scotsmen? Scientific notation may be necessary.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Wait a second.&rdquo; interjects Hayden, as observant as he always is, &ldquo;If you bros are saved, then who&rsquo;s in Heck here?&rdquo;</p>
<p>Shrek&rsquo;s face darkens. &ldquo;Ah laddie&hellip;it&rsquo;s the guy in the pot, a sinner so wicked his own circle of Heck was invented to accommodate him!&rdquo; He picks up a spoon, and pulls a screaming rabbit out of the boiling pot.</p>
<p>Soup slides off of its fur, and revealing none other than Bugs Bunny. His teeth chatter a couple of times.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Nyah, what&rsquo;s up doc?&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Oh, shut ya carrot hole!&rdquo; Exclaims Shrek. &ldquo;Scotus is the only lad here who&rsquo;s a doctor in anything, and you weren&rsquo;t even talking to him! Tell these good people what you&rsquo;ve done.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Nyah&hellip;Okay doc, if you&rsquo;re gonna make me&hellip;So, like, I dropped anvils on people, and I blew up some people, and I manufactured many things which are forbidden by the Geneva Convention while I worked at ACME corp.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&lsquo;Fool!&quot; shrieks Shrek, &ldquo;Tell them the rest, tell them the truth!&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Nyah&hellip;oh yeah&hellip;&rdquo; the rabbit stammers, clearly overwhelmed by the enormity of his guilt. &ldquo;Once&hellip;I shat on a video game reviewer&rsquo;s face in March of 2011.&rdquo;</p>
<p>His misdeeds exposed, Shrek casts the reprobate rabbit back into his pot with a growl of disgust. And there he shall remain for ages of ages.</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty - Five: Demons are a Girl&#39;s Best Friend</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/35/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>As Jack and his ever expanding band of merry men journey their way into the new circle of heck, they hear millions of people throwing up as one. As they come within sight of the darned here, they see a huge mass of pregnant women, all of whom appear to be deep in the throes of morning sickness.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Dear God!&rdquo; exclaims Jack &ldquo;What brought them to this miserable state?&rdquo;</p>
<p>Philip sighs. &ldquo;This is where believers in feminism go - that doctrine which Pastor Jim declared leads women to leave their husbands, kill their babies, practice witchcraft, destroy capitalism, and become lesbians. In service of this false religion, the darned in this circle of Heck refused to be barefoot and pregnant housewives, so now they are forced to be both barefoot and pregnant &hellip; unto eternal ages.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Every woman born after 1993 has bought into feminism &ndash; none of them can cook, all they know is McDonald&rsquo;s. If about half of people are women and two and a half billion people have been born since 1993, how many people will end up here?&rdquo;</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Four: Of Grindr and Meat Grinder</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/34/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NzxcfRt3bRw">Relax to these enchanted beats while reading and working out the math problem for a fuller experience. Or cower in fear of them, if you&rsquo;ve played Terraria</a></p>
<p>Jack and his friends now come upon a lovely, wooded forest. Pixies play in the puddles, alicorns nibble at the grass, and rainbows grace the sky.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Wait a cotton - pickin minute!&rdquo; exclaims Jack &ldquo;This doesn&rsquo;t look like Heck!&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Oh yes, it is.&rdquo; Says Philip &ldquo;This is where gay people and murderers go. Apparently, the powers that be thought that it would be really cruel to force murderers to be in peaceful, enchanted forest forever. Gay people go here because Dante said they went to the same place murderers did a thousand years ago, and nobody bothered to question him since then. The murderers really hate it here, but most of the gay people like it fine.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Then, they see their old friend Hayden there.</p>
<p>&ldquo;HOLY CINNAMON CRUNCH TOAST FUCK!&rdquo; howls Jack &ldquo;HAYDEN, ARE YOU A PRACTICING HOMOSEXUAL!?&rdquo;</p>
<p>Hayden cringes a second and hangs his head in shame. &ldquo;No, I&rsquo;m a murderer.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Jack lets out a sigh of relief and shrugs. &ldquo;Oh, well that&rsquo;s not so bad. How&rsquo;d it happen?&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Well, I became a really famous video game streamer before I died, and one of my top super - chatters decided to stop donating, so I threw him into a meat grinder. I was fleeing the scene on my 500 Euro bicycle, and then that Philip hit me full on with his car, although he tried to swerve away, leading him to smash into the car Chase and Kaegan were in. I got darned to Heck because I didn&rsquo;t learn the world was created last Thursday at Pastor Jim&rsquo;s Bible Church of East Pensacola. If my body weighed 195.5 pounds and accelerated away at 172 m / s second after I got hit, how many newtons of force did Philip hit me with?&rdquo;</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Three: Chase&#39;s Evergaol</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/33/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qGuY3Nin8yU">🍺Listen to this song while working out the math problem, and you may escape the ghastly punishment forced upon Chase by the powers that be🇩🇪</a></p>
<p>Jack and his motley crew walk on into the next circle of Heck, which they know is now home to their old friend Chase. At first, it seems very pleasant. It just looks like a normal bar, though an impeccably clean one.</p>
<p>But then&hellip;they see Chase.</p>
<p>He is seated upon one of the bar stools, wide eyed and terrified. A hose is stuck into his mouth, leading up to the beer kegs. He cannot stop consuming the beer, even if he wishes to. He is forced to imbibe it for eons, and this has done bad things to his body. The poor fella now has the figure of a full water balloon, and thank heavens we don&rsquo;t know what his liver looks like.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Oh, no!&rdquo; Declares Philip, with a macho combination of disgust and sorrow. &ldquo;I now know what happened to this poor, poor fool. Many years ago, he committed a grave sin with no one else ever had - he slandered the German language. He said that it sounded &ldquo;unpleasant&rdquo; and &ldquo;shitty&rdquo; and all sorts of other things. Now, for his offense against the <em>Reich</em>, he is forced to guzzle every last ounce of beer produced by the German nation since its foundation. If every German man, woman, and child produces 10,827 gallons of beer per month (as is common knowledge) and Germany was unified in 1871, how many gallons of beer were there for Chase to drink in 2023? Worse than this, however, is that he must pay for it all, and he will not get out until he pays the last penny.&rdquo;</p>
<p>They think about freeing Chase, but it turns out that Shaggy is Jewish. Therefore, he considers Chase&rsquo;s antisemitic remarks deeply offensive. At his behest, they elect to leave Chase to his ghastly fate.</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Two: La Música del Diablo</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/32/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G1NGE16Bt48">🎵 Escucha a esta canción mientras trabajas en el problema para una experiencia más completa 🎵</a>**</p>
<p>Jack and his motley crew hear howling up ahead. They see a huge mass of red men with horns and pointed tails stabbing people repeatedly with pitchforks. Yet, he also sees his old friend Kaegan sitting next to them, looking extremely bored.</p>
<p>“Yo, bro!” he says, “Chase and I died because Philip slammed into us going 95 a few years back. We got sent to heck because neither of us were members of Pastor Jim’s Bible Church of East Pensacola! I’ve been in this circle of heck ever since then! This is the circle of heck for people who listen to devil music. Now that they’re dead, the devils are teaching them that Satanism isn’t actually fun and gay, it’s actually very sharp and pointy.”</p>
<p>“But, like dude, why aren’t these dudes poking you?” asks Shaggy.</p>
<p>“Okay bro, lemme explain this,” Kaegan says, “So, every time you listen to a piece of devil music, these fellas poke you with a pitchfork 3.636 times every year. But, I like only listened to one devil song while I was in the car with Chase, so mostly this is just really boring. Chase, on the other hand, listened to 82,756 devil songs over his lifetime. If he was here, how many times would the devils poke him every year?”</p>
<p>“Wait, why isn’t Chase here?” Asks Jack.</p>
<p>Kaegan’s face darkens. “He did something scandalous, and now inhabits the next circle of heck.”</p>
<p>Because Kaegen was being poked so rarely, Philip is able to cleverly free him without them caring.</p>
<p>** <!-- raw HTML omitted --> <em>I needed a song that was 1.) not blasphemous 2.) was devil music and 3.) did not contain any naughty words (Pastor Jim&rsquo;s Bible Church of East Pensacola does not approve of those). Esta canción satisface todos de estes criterios con la excepción de tres, pero mi audiencia es un grupo de gringos y no saben la palabra «cabrón.»</em> <!-- raw HTML omitted --></p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-One: The Hivemind</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/31/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jpQQrdglDmw">💀 Ruin your romantic relationships to the rhythm of Reddit&rsquo;s Theme Song while reading and working out this math problem for a fuller experience 💀</a></p>
<p>Before the gate to the next circle of Heck, there stands a morbidly obese titan, one large enough to blow the square cube law to smithereens. Upon his head is a fedora, upon his face, a neckbeard. And, upon his chest is a stained &ldquo;I FUCKING LOVE SCIENCE!&rdquo; t-shirt. His body exudes a stench potent enough to strike down the nations and his armpits are darkened by sweat. His mouth ever whispereth words of blasphemy and the smoke of his cannabis asendeth forever.</p>
<p>“Like ZOINKS dude!” Exclaims Shaggy. “Who, like, are you dude?”</p>
<p>The giant turns toward him with malice in its eyes. “We are the Reddit. We are <strong>LEGION</strong>.”</p>
<p>“Oh. How, like, are you doing?”</p>
<p>It cackles – a painful, bone chilling sound. “<strong>In this moment, we are euphoric! Not because of any phoney God’s blessing, but because we are enlightened by our own intelligence!</strong>&quot; At this, he breaks out into more hideous laughter, as though to demonstrate just how euphoric he is.</p>
<p>“Within us are the souls of all people who have ever made a Reddit account. Joining Reddit is so heinous that the moment a person does it, his soul is sucked down into Heck to be absorbed into us! His body is left behind to be possessed by demons &ndash; nasty, ugly things.&quot; He breaks out into more loathsome cackling, punctuated by a horrible noise in the back his throat, much like a cat coughing up hairballs.</p>
<p>At last, he catches his breath. &ldquo;Granted, this isn&rsquo;t as impressive as it sounds because 74% of all Reddit accounts are bots, and every Redditor has 17 acconts, 16 to upvote his comments &amp; one for porn. If there are 430 million accounts, how many are owned by real people? How many people used Reddit before joining us? What percentage of Reddit accounts are bots? What percentage are for porn?</p>
<p>Immediately after the giant finishes speaking, Philip jumps into action and pulverises him. We, however, are still left to ponder his questions.</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty: The Parable of the Horny Man and Shaggerus</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/30/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack and his compatriots hear cries of pain emanating from the next circle of Heck. “Like zoinks dude!&quot; quoth Shaggy. “I don’t know what these dudes did, but it must’ve been pretty bad!”</p>
<p>Then, they finally come upon the most terrifying sight any of them hath seen thus far in Heck. Ahead of them is a boundless room &ndash; stretching on in all directions to infinity. Every few feet, there standeth a very large and extremely angry mandrill with riding crop in hand, whacking away at some poor bastard&rsquo;s backside like there’s no tomorrow.</p>
<p>“Father Philip!” quoth a prisoner, in betwixt his shrieks of pain. “I didst know thee in life! Father Philip, please, send Shaggy hither that he might apply a dab of ointment to my poor, bruised ass. For I am tormented by this apish brute!”</p>
<p>Philip looketh down upon him with righteous indignation.</p>
<p>“Son, this cannot be done. For thou in thy lifetime didst spank the monkey. Now, in death, &rsquo;tis the monkey who spanketh thee. Thou wert a perennially single and superlatively horny fellow, and thou livedst in a time with top knotch treatment for both tendinitis and carpal tunnel syndrome. Thou didst shuck thy corn 21 times daily, and it was thus for 35 years! How many times didst thou rough up the suspect? For every time thou didst bludgeon thy beefsteak, this monkey shalt bludgeon thee 77 times. Tell me the depth of thy iniquity! Tell me the extent of thy punishment!&quot;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Fine! Fine!&rdquo; quoth the horny man. &ldquo;I pray thee, father, that thou wouldst send Shaggy unto my father’s house! For I have five brethren, all of whom jacketh their beanstalks on the daily. Let him testify unto them lest they also come into this place of torment!&rdquo;</p>
<p>And Philip said unto him, “They hath Lonnie Childs and <a href="https://stopmasturbationnow.org/">stopmasturbationnow.org</a>; let them hear them.”</p>
<p>And the horny man replied, “Nay, father Philip! If one went unto them from the dead, they wouldst repent!”</p>
<p>“Truly I tell thee, if they have not been convinced by Lonnie Childs and <a href="https://stopmasturbationnow.org/">stopmasturbationnow.org</a>, they will not repent even if one rises from the dead.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Besides, I have seen thy brethren&rsquo;s search history. They shalt enjoy it here, methinks.&rdquo;</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Nine: High School Faces Eternity</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/29/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack and his friends finally reach the other side of the black sea. Chocking through the stench, they see the portion of Heck reserved for stupid teenagers. Here are imprisoned all the people who tempted Bloddy Mary, engaged in street racing, listened to Stairway to Heaven backtracked, or made love in that one porta potty off of 494.</p>
<p>Their punishment is to forever be imprisoned within an enlarged version of the average public high school bathroom. Almost every surface is caked in toilet paper, most of which is stained with water, urine, or other, more exotic bodily excretions. The words “Bill ❤️  Tasha” and &ldquo;Trent is a ashole&rdquo; are written on the walls in feces, a substance which is also slathered over the stalls, ceilings, mirrors, and floors at irregular intervals. Worst of all, however, are the circle’s inhabitants. They are morbidly obese, unhealthy creatures, with clothing and flesh as filthy as their surroundings.</p>
<p>Jack coughs a little. &ldquo;Smells like teen spirit.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Let us assume that this circle of Heck was opened in 1960 and that its inhabitants then produced five metric tons of bodily excretions every year. If this number increased exponentially every decade, how many metric tons of bodily excretions would those darned in this circle of Heck produce in the year 2020? If a third of that was not properly flushed, how many metric tons of bodily excretions would be left in this circle of Heck in 2020?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Eight: Christmas Special!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/28/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>A morbidly obese male ghost appears before Jack, dressed in what would appear to be a dirty hospital gown. &ldquo;I am the ghost of Christmas future. Grasp the side of my gown, and you shall see the shape of things to come if your quest is unsuccessful.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Jack thinks about it for a second. &ldquo;Fine, I&rsquo;d like to get out of Heck for a while. It can&rsquo;t be worse than this.&rdquo; So, he obeys the ghost, and his surroundings disappear in a rushing wind. His eyes open to a terrifying scene.</p>
<p>He stands before an open - air stage in Geneva. The sky above the city is the color of a television tuned to a dead channel. The masses around him have been successfully culled &ndash; soy products, vaccines, and Elon Musk&rsquo;s neuralink implants have deprived them of all independent thinking. If their dead, empty eyes are any guide, none of these people can even conceive of sticking their genitalia into KFC deep fryers. Freedom is dead.</p>
<p>Up onto the stage steps Klaus Schwab - the slanderer, the strongman, the god of this world! In his right hand he holds a pitchfork, in his left a Dungeons and Dragons rulebook. He is arrayed all in black, and his horns can clearly be seen protruding from his head.</p>
<p>He begins to speak. &ldquo;Hello my vondrous underlings, I have an announcement to make to you. Zis night, Santa Klaus - ze inferior Klaus - shall attempt to bring candy canes to ze children. Zis is foolish and unnecessary. Children have no need of candy canes, zey have all ze bugs zey could possibly vant to eat back home in zeir pods.&rdquo;</p>
<p>At this, the crowd goes wild, for eating bugs is the only thing they still have any enthusiasm for, after all these years of being fed their high - fructose corn syrup and denied their horse dewormer. But, the archon raises his hand, and they fall silent.</p>
<p>&ldquo;But afzer tonight, ze inferior Klaus shall bozer us no more. Indeed, I zink I see him coming right over ze city now.&rdquo;</p>
<p>And, the Dark Lord speaks truth. As Jack looks on, a flying red sleigh exits hyperspace 704 feet above the ground. Elon Musk, who has long since forsaken the weakness of his flesh for the cold certainty of steel, is standing 1253 feet due south from Santa. Musk raises his right robotic arm and lets a high intensity laser beam fly at his the jolly old elf. Less than a second later, the sleigh becomes a fireball, and its entourage begin plummeting toward the ground at breakneck speeds. Cries of &ldquo;HO! HO! HO!&rdquo; and &ldquo;WWWWEEEEHHHH!&rdquo; echo throughout Geneva.</p>
<p>Assuming that Santa was unable to move any since his exit of hyperspace, and that the intersection of his height and distance from Elon form a right triangle, how much distance did Elon&rsquo;s laser beam have to travel?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Seven: The Black Lake of Degnerates</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/27/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack and his companions see a great black lake in front of them, on the other side of which lie the circles of Heck dedicated to degenerate high school students. At first they think it is impassable, but then they see a motorboat sitting there. Philip, who knows the way Heck works very well, says that this is how they’re meant to cross. So, they all get into it and start sailing. At first, all seems well, but then they are overcome with a putrid, horrible smell. All of them fall over with tears in their eyes except for Philip, who maintains his stoic calm.</p>
<p>“What’s like, happening dude?” Shaggy asks through his coughs and tears.</p>
<p>“That is the stench of the degenerates.” Responds Philip. “Every fifteen minutes, 0.8% of the air we breath becomes replaced by the horrid stench of the next circle of Heck. If we will only reach 100% degenerate stench when we are on the other side of the sea, how long will it be?”</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems//#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Six: Of Sinners and Samurai</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/26/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="%5Bhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oKW6gLLmxDQ">A Swedish heavy metal band liked this math problem so much they based a song on it. Listen to it while working the problem out for a fuller experience</a></p>
<p>As Jack and his allies come upon a large clearing, the sounds of clashing metal and yelling reach their ears. They see a legion of men dressed in traditional Japanese armor, wielding katanas and 17th century firearms. Opposite them stand a throng of monsters, resembling human beings, but with bulbous, empty eyes; gaping, slobberous mouths; and bulging secondary sex characteristics. On they shamble, hearts filled with nothing but a base hatred for their foes.</p>
<p>“You are on path to destruction, oni chan!” One of the monsters exclaims.</p>
<p>“<em>Nani</em>!?” cries Jack in abject horror. &ldquo;What are these monsters?&rdquo;</p>
<p>Philip sighs in a empathetic yet ruggedly masculine way. “These are the souls of zoomers and Samurai. The zoomers lusted after Japanese cartoons in their hearts, so now they have been transformed into them in death. Opposite them stand so many brave Samurai, who are now forced to see what their once – great nation has exported to the world. These two armies will fight forever more, killing each other every day and rising to fight again each morning.</p>
<p>A volley of gunfire crashes into the zoomers, and several of them fall. Yet, another is enraged. It contorts its body into a bizarre, disturbing position and screams “You will grovel before us, for we are men of culture! Know your fate! YOU DDDIIIEEE!!! CURSE YE HA ME HA!”</p>
<p>A blast of white light extends from its hands, and several Samurai burst into pillars of ash, obliterated by a burst of unbearable misfortune.</p>
<p>“Like, will these dudes ever like get into hand-to-hand combat?” Shaggy asks.</p>
<p>“Oh yes, eventually.” Philip responds. “The zoomers are advancing toward the Samurai at an average pace of 13 miles per hour. If the Samurai are three and a half miles away from them, about how long will it take them to reach their foes?”</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Five: Of Goth and Goth Hunter</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/25/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>(Note 🗒️: Nevermind. I found a funny stereotype about Gen Xers)</p>
<p>Next up in their journey through Heck, Jack and the gang find themselves in a rainy field filled with the sound of terrible wailing. There is a huge fence, separating those on one side of the field from the other. On one side, there are a horde of souls who were once goths in life. The wear sopping wet, black clothes, with makeup and hair dye running down their bodies. On the other side, there stand a horde of overweight men, all of them wailing in despair.</p>
<p>Philip sheds a single intense yet manly tear. “The Lord has a cruel sense of humor,” he says in a baleful tone. “Here, the goths tormented are forever on their side of the fence. They must eternally put up with the rain messing up their makeup, hair dye, and other cosmetic substances. The men on the other side of the fence, by contrast, yearned for nothing more than a simple goth gf. And now, they are forced dwell within sight of those they sought after so long. Yet, the goths will not speak to them nor make love to them, for they are overcome with sorrow.”</p>
<p>As if in response to this, one of the darned lets up out deep, moist - sounding bellow of despair. &ldquo;No Goth gf! Let Grog have goth gf!&rdquo;</p>
<p>“Wait a sec.” Jack says, “It looks like there are way more goth hunters than goths.”</p>
<p>“Oh yes,” Philip responds, “For every one goth, there are 4*10^8 goth hunters. If there are half a million goths, how many goth hunters must there be?”</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Four: Millennial Darn</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/24/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>(Note 🗒️: Gen Xers were skipped due to my inability to think of amusing stereotypes about them)</p>
<p>Our motley crew has moved on from the boomer fishery and made their way into the next circle of Heck. At first, it seems to be a perfectly normal town, filled with people raising children and doing their jobs. But then, Jack sees that all of the adults have tears streaming down their faces.</p>
<p>“What is this madness?” Jack asks. “Who are these people and why are they so depressed?”</p>
<p>“These,” says Philip, who is so wise that he knows the ins and outs of the whole afterlife, “are Millennials. In life, they refused to have children or jobs and to get off of their parents’ cellular plans. So now, for eternity, they are doomed to work, have families, and pay their own bills.”</p>
<p>A fat man at a hotdog stand checks his phone and bursts into tears. “No! No! My parents won’t let me stay on their Hulu subscription anymore! I’d been on that thing for seventeen years, and it cost $79.99 every year! How much money did they save me?” The poor man lets out a blood-curdling wail. “If I’m going to spend every minute of my spare time watching Hulu for a hundred and seventy-two years, how much will I pay!”</p>
<p>The poor man collapses onto his hotdog stand, overcome by the enormity of his loss, leaving Jack to calculate how much money his parents saved him.</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Three: Whatever ya say, Boomer</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/23/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Having moved beyond purgatory and Limbo, Jack, Philip, and Shaggy head down into Heck itself. At first, they appear to be on the side of a normal river. But then, Jack realizes that there are large, anthropomorphic fish and crawdads sitting on the shore, fishing for people swimming around in the water.</p>
<p>“Uh sir,” Jack asks one of them, “what’s going on?”</p>
<p>“Well, this is the first circle of Heck. The first few circles aren’t for sins people have individually committed, but rather generational sins they have inherited. This circle of Heck is where unrepentant boomers are eternally punished. In life, they fished for us, so now we fish for them.” As he finishes, the fish puts a 1960s – era nudie mag on the hook and casts it out into the water.</p>
<p>“Yo, that’s some, like, real gnarly bait bro!” Shaggy says. “What else ya got?”</p>
<p>“We have a total of 17,041 pieces of bait.” The fish says. “26% are nudie mags, 14% are Beatles albums, 27% are Vietnam war memorabilia, 13% are parts of classic cars, and 20% are tie-dye shirts.”</p>
<p>“But like, I wanna know the raw numbers dude.”</p>
<p>“You’ll just have to do the math yourself!”</p>
<p>Just as Shaggy gets his notebook and pen out, a boomer latches onto a Vietnam war protest sign, and is pulled screaming out of the water. With cruel glee, the fish haul out a boom box.</p>
<p>“Oh hello Evans, I’m so happy to see you again.” The fish says with a cruel smile. “We’re gonna make you listen to that newfangled whippersnapper music now!”</p>
<p>The boomer screams, but his cry is cut off by a blaring Tekashi69 song. Jack and his companions cover their ears in pain, but it isn’t enough to save them.</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-Two: Enter Gigaphil</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/22/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OVh0bMNSFss">💪 For a fuller experience, lift to these virile tunes while reading and working out the math problem 💪</a></p>
<p>After wading through the corn – seas of purgatory for what feels like an eternity, Jack and Shaggy finally reach Limbo. Limbo appears to be a huge, indoor gym. For a second, they think that it’s empty, but then, they hear someone deadlifting in the distance. They follow the sound until, at long last, they see a huge beast of a man there. Standing at least eight feet tall, the man - beast is in enough muscle to make Arnold Schwarzenegger green with envy and even the straightest of men say things which sound slightly homoerotic. At first, Jack thinks the man’s barbell is loaded down with weights, but then he realizes there’s actually a minivan one either side.</p>
<p>The man - if he is a man at all - turns toward them for a second, and Jack realizes that it’s his old friend, Philip.</p>
<p>“Philip!” Jack exclaims, “How’d you end up in Limbo?”</p>
<p>“Well, ten years ago, I was killed in a car crash on my way home from a Dungeons and Dragons game. Because of that transgression, and my lack of membership in Pastor Jim&rsquo;s Bible Church of East Pensacola, I was forbidden from receiving the beatific vision. But, Saint Peter determined I was too much of a chad to be darned to Heck, so I was instead cast into Limbo for eternity. Five years ago, the Lord came unto me in a vision, and told me I had been called to help you oppose Klaus Schwab and his Luciferian Agenda. So, I began lifting to better fight the good fight when the time comes.</p>
<p>“If each of these minivans weighs 3872 pounds, and I’ve been lifting them both every thirty seconds for the past five years, how many times have I lifted them? How much total weight have I lifted?&quot;</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twenty-One: Purgatorio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/21/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RfCiefs0k3k"> 🌽 Shuck to these midwestern beats while <em>working out</em> the math problem for a fuller experience 🌽</a></p>
<p>Jack and Shaggy find themselves in purgatory, which looks identical to rural Iowa. Corn stretches in all directions as far as the eye can see.</p>
<p>“Like, where the zoinks are we supposed go dude?” Shaggy asks.</p>
<p>Queen Elizabeth II stumbles through the shoots of corn. &ldquo;Tally-ho, young sir! What were you saying?” she asks.</p>
<p>“We’re on a mission from God that requires us to go through Heck, and we have no clue how to get there from here.”</p>
<p>“Well, Purgatory is the spiritual equivalent of the American corn-growing states, and Heck is much hotter than them, so I figure you have to just go south for a long time.”</p>
<p>“How like, much corn is there here man?” Shaggy asks.</p>
<p>“Firstly, you must know the bizarre way Purgatory works. The landscape is almost entirely ripped from the American Midwest, but it had to be enlarged to accommodate many penetrant sinners, so that now it is 18^6 times larger than its counterpart in the world of the living, which is 610,080 square miles. If, on average, each acre produces 198 bushels of corn, and a square mile contains 640 acres, how many bushels of corn would there be? If every bushel of corn contains 90,000 kernels, how many kernels are there?”</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problems Nineteen and Twenty: Sandwich Man at the Bridge of Death</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/1920/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/1920/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Saint Peter points Jack in the general direction of Purgatory, handing him a special ID card to let the angels know he isn’t a darned soul trying to escape Heck. After some time, Jack comes to the Brig o&rsquo; Dread, where there is a border patrol station between Heaven and Purgatory.</p>
<p>Just ahead of him, Jack sees Shaggy. &ldquo;Like zoinks dude, this is super dooper ungroovy!&rdquo; he says &ldquo;Scoobs must have put some gnarly edibles on my sandwich, because I just hallucinated that Saint Peter condemned my immortal soul to 10,000 years in purgatory!&rdquo;</p>
<p>“Uh, Shaggy,” Jack says, “I dunno how to break it to you, but that wasn’t a hallucination! This is the afterlife!”</p>
<p>“Zoinks! I’m, like &hellip; dead?” Shaggy begins sobbing inconsolably. “Oh, I know how it must have happened. I’d like just got back from rehab for food addiction, and I’d lost like a bagillion pounds! They told me my stomach had shrunk to a tenth of its original size, which was exactly 40.436 cubic meters! But see, when I got home, Scobby made me a sandwich, and I thought it’d be fine to eat it because it was vegan and healthy and everything. But Scobby still made it in the portion size I used to eat, which was 26.728 cubic meters, and I like slurped it down in one bite! How many times larger than my small, puny stomach must it have been? If every 2 cubic meters of super Shaggy Sandwich contains 500 calories, how many calories did I consume?”</p>
<hr>
<p>Jack does the math in his head, and something strikes him. “Wait, Shaggy, how in the name of God could your stomach be forty cubic meters? You’re a skinny dude.”</p>
<p>“People ask me that all the time. Truth is that I’m a demi-god, and my stomach’s way bigger on the inside than it is on the outside!”</p>
<p>“Bro, I’m on a quest from the Lord to save the world, and having a demigod with me would be really helpful! Let’s tell the border patrol agent that, and maybe he’ll let you join me! I get help and you get a get out of purgatory free card.”</p>
<p>The tears stop flowing down Shaggy’s face. “Groovy dude!”</p>
<p>They eventually reach the crossing booth, and come face to face with a crouching Russian man wearing white Adidas.</p>
<p>“Papers, please.” he says.</p>
<p>Jack hands over the card Saint Peter gave him.</p>
<p>“What you think this is? These are the special cards Saint Peter give out to people on special mission from God. You clearly not one of those, punk. Get better at forging documents.”</p>
<p>The man is just about to order Jack cast off the Brig o&rsquo; Dread and into Heck. But then his eyes lay on Shaggy.</p>
<p>“Oh, that you Shaggy? I you biggest fan! Everyone love you, Shaggy! Admittedly, only about third of Russians know you exist, but there about 187,000,000 people in Russia (including Ukrainians, of course), so you just do the math yourself! That a lot of people!</p>
<p>“Shaggy, if you believe this man is trustworthy, I trust you. You both continue on through purgatory.”</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Eighteen: Paradiso</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/18/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BNZVVV5WUqk">😇 Relax to these ethereal, heavenly tunes on loop while working out the math problem for a fuller experience 😇</a></p>
<p>Jack has finally gotten to the end of the tunnel of light, and now he sees the pearly gates before him. The breathtaking display of heavenly glory is only dampened by an angry-looking Middle Eastern man in a toga.</p>
<p>“Hey, newly deceased sinner, get ready to be judged!” He hollers at Jack. “I’m Saint Peter, and your arse is about to find out real fast whether it’s destined for eternal darnnation in Heck or heavenly bliss!”</p>
<p>He pauses to go through his notes. “You named Jack?” He asks.</p>
<p>“Yeah.” Jack says.</p>
<p>“Well, newly deceased sinner, looks like you do stand guilty of plenty of sins against God and man. And you never was a member of Pastor Jim&rsquo;s Bible Church of East Pensacola, outside of which there is no salvation.</p>
<p>&ldquo;But, it’s your lucky day, because the Lord needs you to go on a mission for him. See, when you was on earth, you kept the powers of darkness in check. But, now that you’re gone all the archons stand completely unopposed! (You know, Bill Clinton, Klaus Schwab, Joe Biden, Jeff Bezos, that bunch?) If nothing is done to stop them, they will summon the antichrist in 38 minutes.</p>
<p>“In order to stop them, you must enlist the aid of two souls you knowed when you was alive. One of ‘em is waiting for ya down in Limbo, but the other is languishing in the deepest, darkest pit of Heck. Once you’ve freed both of them, you will be returned to earth to do battle with them Powers and Principalities.”</p>
<p>“Wait a second!” Jack exclaims “How do you expect me to get through the whole bad section of the afterlife in 38 minutes?”</p>
<p>“Oh brotha, don’t worry about that. Time passes differently here in the afterlife. For every second that passes down on earth, a three leap years pass up here. Just do the math yourself! You’ve got plenty of time!”</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-four-the-harrowing-of-heck">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
