<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Math Problems Season 3 on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/math-problems-season-3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Math Problems Season 3 on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>David McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/math-problems-season-3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.png</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Seventeen: The Passion of the Jack</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/17/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZbR5WcyWl18">🎵 For a Fuller Experience, Jam to These Retro Tunes While Reading and Working out the Math Problem 🎵</a></p>
<p>As Bill Clinton arrives at Jack’s home, the earth begins to shake. Church bells begin to toll in the distance - a hollow, threatening sound. The sky is stained a dusky green, the color of unpaid tax dollars. The Majora’s Mask Final Hours Theme begins to play loudly, perhaps produced by some ethereal DJ studio.</p>
<p>As Bill Clinton gets out of his car, Jack begins second guessing himself. <em>Yes</em>, he thinks, <em>I may be the god-emperor of mankind, but does that mean I am the strongest of the gods? Could there be powers in this world older and stronger than mine? Is there a bigger fish?</em></p>
<p>Jack watches with apprehension as the door’s handle turns and it creaks open. He raises his sword to defend himself, but it is too late. An eldritch blast emanates from Bill Clinton, exerting 285,295 Newtons of force upon Jack’s soul. If Jack’s soul weights 21.3 grams and is unaffected by friction, both properties souls are widely known to display, how fast will it fly away from his body?</p>
<p>&hellip;</p>
<p>The room around Jack vanishes. All he can hear is Bill Clinton’s maniacal laughter and that cursed music. But, the first of these fades away, while the later grows louder.</p>
<p>Jack sees a tunnel of light, and he knows this isn’t the end. Yet, his heart freezes. After his use of heroin, his piracy, his idolatry to Jimmy Wales, his deception of Death Himself, and his apotheosis in the minds of the people, Jack does not believe the Abrahamic God will allow him to escape judgment for his sins. As he nears the light, he tries desperately to go back, but to no avail.</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems#season-three-jackhammer-40k">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Sixteen: The Beginning of the End</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/16/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The tax man flies off into the night at a breakneck speed and passes over the horizon. Suddenly, Jack’s phone starts ringing, and he answers it.</p>
<p>“Jackie boy, I am Bill Clinton, and I know what you just did. I’m coming up there to learn you the right way to treat government officials.”</p>
<p>Bill will be unable to start driving for thirty-six hours because his attractive female intern is visiting the dry cleaners’ in his car. Once he gets it back, Bill will start driving from his presidential library in Little Rock, Arkansas to Jack’s House in Belcarra, British Columbia. Belcarra and Little Rock are 2,396.69 Miles apart, and Bill Clinton will be driving at twenty miles per hour the whole way, making no stops. In how many days will Bill Clinton reach Jack?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-three-jackhammer-40k">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Fifteen: Our Hero Changes his Mind</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/15/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The tax man  greedily snatches Jack&rsquo;s check out of his hands. He turns around and scampers away, his four chins swaying like hay in the wind. But, as his blubbery hand flops onto the door knob, Jack has a change of heart. His body accelerates from a standstill to 1,373 meters per second toward the taxman. If Jack weighs 62 kilograms, how many newtons of force will he exert upon the tax man&rsquo;s body when they make contact, assuming that the air exercises 15 newtons of drag on him?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-three-jackhammer-40k">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Fourteen: The One Joke you Have to Make About Money in the Future</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/14/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The tax man completes the previous math problem, and Jack sighs, knowing he’s been beat. He produces a checkbook and writes away 32 trillion dollars. Granted, this isn’t an especially large amount of money nowadays. Since hyperinflation started in 2020, twenty-five years ago, every year the value of the dollar has been an eighth of what it was the year before. What is the amount of money Jack owes equivalent to in 2020 dollars?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-three-jackhammer-40k">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirteen: Of Triangles and Taxes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/13/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>One day, Jack walks into his bedroom to find the IRS man standing there, waiting to pounce. He says that Jack&rsquo;s ex-wife owed Bill Clinton 32 trillion dollars in taxes, and that since Jack is marked as her next of kin, he has to pay up. &ldquo;I know you&rsquo;re the god emperor of mankind and all that jazz now,&rdquo; he says, &ldquo;but these are outstanding debts from before that, so you still have to pay up.&rdquo; Jack asks how he came to owe this money, and the tax man heaves a heavy sigh.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Well, after you went to prison, you ex became romantically involved with Bill Clinton. But, their relationship ended on less than favorable terms, and after all that Bill&rsquo;s been through over the past few decades, that was the last straw. He had a psychotic break and assigned large amounts of tax debt to people for arbitrary reasons. In your ex-wife&rsquo;s case, he assigned it based on the area of a certain isosceles triangle.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;What? How?&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Well, the base of the triangle was 8 trillion units across, but we don&rsquo;t know what its height was. All we know is that its area totalled to 32 trillion units, ergo the 32 trillion dollars you now owe to the IRS.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Jack thought for a second. &ldquo;This sounds phony, like those YouTube ads I get saying that if I click on them beautiful Asian women will have sex with me. If you can tell me what the height of that triangle was, I&rsquo;ll think about paying up, but otherwise you&rsquo;re gonna be in a world of hurt.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The tax man sighed. &ldquo;I was afraid of this. Now I&rsquo;ll have to do math!&rdquo;</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-three-jackhammer-40k">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Twelve: To Answer This one, we Need to Talk About Parallel Universes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/12/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack has absorbed Jimmy Wales’ essence and become a literal god. He rules the world with an iron fist. But, there is still one thing which his heart desires, one thing which he needs. He needs to finally take revenge on his ex - wife. He must make her pay for what she did to him. Jack couldn’t find any information about her whereabouts, so he captured her family and forced them to watch the Bee Movie until they told him where she was.</p>
<p>But to answer that question, we need to talk about parallel universes. As a bizarre consequence of some law of physics or another,  if you go travel at a speed greater than 2,917 kilometers per hour at the equator, you will be transported into a parallel universe. Jack’s ex traveled twenty four parallel universes (6QPU) away from Jack. The only known way to build up enough speed to do this is by backward long jumping. You see, if one backwards long jumps fast enough, they won’t gain any kinetic energy but will instead gain potential energy. When you stop backward long jumping, all of your potential energy will instead become kinetic. If every one of Jack’s backward long jumps would carry him a hundred yards in three seconds, (Jack is the god emperor of mankind, don’t question it), how many backward long jumps will it take to transport him to his wife’s parallel universe?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-three-jackhammer-40k">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermission Two: Jack&#39;s Revenge</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/12-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/12-5/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack backward long jumps many times, and then he stops. All of the force hits
him immediately. He sees the parallel universes laid out before him and is
aware of his traversing them. Then, a second later, he is on the ground in
another world.</p>
<p>Jack feels in his bones that his ex wife is close. After just a few minutes of
searching, he sees her: his nemesis. It was she that got him addicted to heroin
tricked him into stealing his mothers wedding ring. Jack&rsquo;s power blazes forth.
His laser eyes begin to power up and he raises his sword. But, he hesitates. It
would be terribly cruel to destroy his ex this way. So instead, like a certain
long forgotten Zelda boss, she is cast into the gap between dimensions.</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-three-jackhammer-40k">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
