<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Ethics on AlvinMcGee.xyz</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/ethics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ethics on AlvinMcGee.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Alvin McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 23:57:03 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/ethics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.svg</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Innocuous Things Consistent Conservative Catholics&#39; Should Condemn</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/pf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 23:57:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/pf/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Though it is today most associated with conservative Catholics [1], Christians historically condemned contraception, homosexuality, and a panoply of other sex acts as &ldquo;unnatural.&rdquo; Modern people sometimes understand this to mean that they don&rsquo;t occur in the natural world or fall outside the bounds of normal human behavior. Of course, these are silly reasons to be morally opposed to something and neither imply Catholic sexual ethics.</p>
<p>But, this is <em>not</em> what the Catholic Church is trying to say. Instead, based on an ethical system called Natural Law theory, they say it&rsquo;s wrong to use our organs or faculties in a way which violates their natural purpose. Different opponents of contraception nuance this in different ways &ndash; some say it&rsquo;s wrong to use our organs for ends <em>other than</em> their function, others that we merely cannot use them in ways <em>contrary to</em> their function. This still seems odd, but it has the advantage of mostly delivering the verdicts conservative Catholics are looking for [2]. Unfortunately, it also condemns a wide spectrum of human behavior which seems innocuous or positive. These include, but are likely not limited to:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Cutting one&rsquo;s hair or Shaving.</strong> Your hair follicles have the obvious function of producing hair; shaving your hair is directly contrary to this. Do teenage boys just have to look weird and scruffy for awhile?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Trimming one&rsquo;s nails.</strong> <em>Mutatis mutandis,</em> what I said about shaving applies here.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Licking rocks.</strong> We in the geoscience biz regularly lick rocks to help identify them. But clearly isn&rsquo;t what tongues are for, tongues are for talking and eating. Perhaps it isn&rsquo;t contrary to eating and talking, but it&rsquo;s certainly distinct from them.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Wearing earplugs.</strong> Earplugs interfere with one&rsquo;s ability to hear things, which is the natural end of ears. A natural law theorist can probably justify earplug usage around power tools and rock bands because this protects one&rsquo;s hearing. But, she surely must condemn someone who occasionally wears headphones because he enjoys the quiet, in order to help him concentrate, or so that he might better enjoy his music. It&rsquo;s unclear whether she must condemn people who wear earplugs to cope with painfully sensitive hearing (as I must); perhaps she could appeal to the <em>principle of totality,</em> which states that it is permissible to destroy, dismember, or debilitate an organ when it is necessary for the good of the person (this is why natural law theorists don&rsquo;t go around protesting the amputation of gangrenous limbs). As a hyperacusic person, I can assure you it would be painful and debilitating if I couldn&rsquo;t don earplugs when I encountered a gas - powered leaf blower or a car alarm. But, as pregnancy is pretty debilitating, ends painfully, and sometimes results injury or death [3], this response probably forces the natural law theorist to condone birth control.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Wearing sunglasses.</strong> <em>Mutatis mutandis,</em> most of what I said about earplugs applies here.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Enjoying bitter foods.</strong> We&rsquo;re able to taste bitter foods because, in our deep evolutionary past, this deterred us from eating poisonous things. If you develop a taste for orange rinds or something, you&rsquo;re your taste buds in a manner directly contrary to their natural end. (This probably also applies to enjoying spicy food)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Wearing antiperspirants.</strong> Your sweat glands are supposed to, well, sweat. Stopping them is clearly a crime against nature and a mortal sin! At least it indirectly makes avoiding contraception easier &hellip; [4]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Getting circumcised.</strong> The natural end of a man&rsquo;s foreskin is to cover his glans at &ndash; shall we say &ndash; most times. Circumcision quite obviously perverts this end, making it thoroughly unnatural. This wouldn&rsquo;t only apply to circumcisions performed on infants, which many people understandably oppose, but also to those performed on adult men get with their continuous and enthusiastic consent.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Natural Family Planning.</strong> Natural Family Planning, more commonly known as the rhythm method of birth control, is the Catholic Church&rsquo;s approved brand of birth control. It involves a woman tracking her monthly cycle to avoid having sex while ovulating. While not especially effective, it represents an attempt to have sex without having children. I have heard some Catholics justify this by claiming that other methods of contraception are wrong because they are artificial, whilst natural family planning is not. But this makes little sense, it takes us back to the silly caricatures of Natural Law Theory I mentioned at the beginning of this post.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Using painkillers.</strong> We are designed to experience pain around negative stimuli, but aspirins, Advil, and anesthesia look rebel against nature to make our lives more tolerable. Sometimes, a natural law theorist may be able to justify painkillers with the aforementioned principle of totality, but not always; it might, for instance, only justify killing especially debilitating pains.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<p>[1]: Most other Christians softened or abandoned this line of thought during the 20th century, something my Protestant self is thankful for. Occasionally conservative Protestants say similar things about homosexuality, but Protestant opposition to contraception &amp; non - penetrative sex is critically endangered. I believe Tibetan Buddhists &amp; some Orthodox Jews have similar ideas, but I am less well - informed about them.)</p>
<p>[2]: It&rsquo;s controversial among philosophers whether organs have natural functions in the way natural lawyers need them to (indeed, my impression is modern philosophers tend to thing <em>they don&rsquo;t</em>). And, given how many people naturally experience sex dreams, it seems far from obvious that procreation is the natural function of sex in the narrow sense opponents of contraception need it to be. But, for the purposes of this post, I&rsquo;m not interested in arguing either of those points.</p>
<p>[3]: This applies more to the pre - modern world and in developing countries than it does in the industrialized world, but childbearing remains painful and dangerous even there.</p>
<p>[4]: Actually, as masturbation is equally contrary to nature, this logic is questionable at best.</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
