<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Philosophy on AlvinMcGee.xyz</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/philosophy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Philosophy on AlvinMcGee.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Alvin McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/philosophy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.svg</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Empty or Half Full? Philosophers respond.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/phil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/phil/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In our quest to find out whether the glass was half empty or half full, we first asked the world&rsquo;s great philosophers. Here are their responses.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Leibniz says: This is the fullest of all possible glasses.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Schopenhauer says: Everything sucks, including the glass.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Thales says: The glass is completely full because the air in the top half is also water.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The mereological nihilist says: There is no glass.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The ontological nihilist says: I couldn&rsquo;t have said it better than the previous guy, except what I think doesn&rsquo;t stop sounding crazy if I spend fifteen minutes explaining it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Aristotle says: The glass is actually half empty but possesses the potentiality to be half full.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Anselm says: In using this vessel as part of thine shitty comedy operation, thou hast offended its unfathomably great honor. (<em>sighs</em>) Looks like we&rsquo;re gonna have to set you on fire, bud.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The logical positivist says: Your question is not only extremely annoying but also utterly meaningless.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Michael Huemer says: It just seems really obvious that the glass is half full.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The panpsychist says: Why don&rsquo;t you just ask him, man?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Plato says: The glass halfway participates in the form of fullness.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>John Rawls says: The glass would agree to be half full.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Spinoza says: On God or nature, you brought me back to life just to ask me that?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The solipsist says: The glass doesn&rsquo;t exist and neither do you. Oh, you disagree with that? That&rsquo;s just what a nonexistent person would say.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Lance Bush says: The notion of a &ldquo;full glass&rdquo; is completely unintelligible.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The analytic philosopher says: Okay, let&rsquo;s unpack this a little &hellip; [begins a seven hour monologue discussing the precise usage of the terms involved and their history, making heavy use of symbolic logic and Bayes&rsquo; Theorem all the while. His conclusion: &ldquo;I dunno bro, it&rsquo;s probably just semantics or something.&rdquo;]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The continental philosopher says: Hark upon the serendipitous quintessence with which we must congitate upon such a query - multitudinous intrepid spirits hath ruminated upon this antique problem passim the eons; for the portion of this individuated subjectivity, think he that the chalice mays perchance be halfway empty - if considered from a certain point of view, but that, in pure disreflective beingness - if perchance such a thing might there be - the query musts finally remain unanswered; or perhaps there is no that such to be gobbledegooked; perchance instead it be that gobbledebooking shall not maintain apace of the clandestine ruminations liken to &hellip; [he continues on like this for the next fifteen minutes, liberally using many obscure words and several he just made up (as well as all punctuation marks save periods). One of our interns gets the best sleep of her life. Towards the end he begins shouting in French, throws the glass out the window, and faints]</p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
