<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Apologetics on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/apologetics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apologetics on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>David McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 22:09:34 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/apologetics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.png</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>All the Blood Drained from the Young Man&#39;s Face</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/all-the-blood-drained-from-the-young-mans-face/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 22:09:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/all-the-blood-drained-from-the-young-mans-face/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>For a while, the Christian apologist Frank Turek would occasionally repost this tweet:</p>
<!-- raw HTML omitted -->
<p><img src="/blood.png" alt="All the blood drained from the young man&rsquo;s face"></p>
<p>Whether this story is real or apocryphal, Turek is making a <em>very serious</em> point. Many young people abandon Christianity, or at least its historic positions about sexual morality, on account of ingrained horniness.</p>
<p>But, I confess I&rsquo;ve always found the Tweet a little hilarious. And I think it deserves to be parodied and dramatically read until Kingdom come. I&rsquo;ve gotten us started, but don&rsquo;t let that stop you from pitching in!</p>
<hr>
<p>&ldquo;You&rsquo;re raising all of these objections because you&rsquo;re sleeping with your girlfriend. Am I right?&rdquo;</p>
<p>All the blood flowed to the young man&rsquo;s face.</p>
<p>Frank was wrong.</p>
<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m rejecting God because he gave me Peyroine&rsquo;s disease.&rdquo;</p>
<hr>
<p>&ldquo;You&rsquo;re raising all of these objections because Jim plays the drums so loud, am I right?&rdquo;</p>
<p>All the blood drained from the young aspie&rsquo;s face.</p>
<p>He was caught.</p>
<p>He was rejecting God because he couldn&rsquo;t stand God&rsquo;s sound system.</p>
<hr>
<p>&ldquo;You&rsquo;re raising all of these objections because you want to keep your foreskin. Am I right?</p>
<p>All the blood drained from the young man&rsquo;s face.</p>
<p>He was caught.</p>
<p>He was rejecting Allah because he didn&rsquo;t like Allah&rsquo;s morality.</p>
<hr>
<p>&ldquo;You&rsquo;re raising all these objections because you hate bonnets. Am I right?&rdquo;</p>
<p>All the blood drained form the young woman&rsquo;s face.</p>
<p>She was caught.</p>
<p>She was rejecting God because she didn&rsquo;t share God&rsquo;s fashion sense.</p>
<hr>
<p>&ldquo;You&rsquo;re raising all these objections because you hate weed. Am I right?&rdquo;</p>
<p>All the blood drained from the young man&rsquo;s face.</p>
<p>He was caught.</p>
<p>He was rejecting Jah because he didn&rsquo;t like Jah&rsquo;s morality.</p>
<hr>
<p>&ldquo;You&rsquo;re raising all of these objections because you want a blood transfusion, am I right?&rdquo;</p>
<p>All the blood drained from the young anemic&rsquo;s face.</p>
<p>She was caught.</p>
<p>She was rejecting Jehovah because she didn&rsquo;t want to die.</p>
<hr>
<p>&ldquo;You&rsquo;re raising all of these objections because you wear prophylactics. Am I right?&rdquo;</p>
<p>All the blood drained from the old man&rsquo;s face.</p>
<p>He was caught.</p>
<p>He was rejecting God because he didn&rsquo;t like God&rsquo;s morality.</p>
<hr>
<p>&ldquo;You&rsquo;re raising all of these objections because you&rsquo;re sleeping with your girlfriend. Am I right?&rdquo;</p>
<p>Both the eyes rolled in the young man&rsquo;s face.</p>
<p>He was pissed.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Frank, we&rsquo;ve been through this. I&rsquo;m still ace.&rdquo;</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
