<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Math Problems on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/math-problems/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Math Problems on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>David McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/math-problems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.png</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Nine: Cornpop is a Bad Dude</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/39/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/39/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack and his crew steal Elon Musk&rsquo;s fastest UFO and return once more to the Earth. They land on Jeffery Epstein&rsquo;s island - now restored to its previous glory - to find Joe Biden and Bill Clinton standing in front of the door.</p>
<p>&ldquo;What the hell kid?&rdquo; asks Bill Clinton. &ldquo;I thought you died!&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;I was once slain, but now I live. I am Jack, conqueror of death!&rdquo;</p>
<p>Bill is about to respond, but he&rsquo;s cut off by the other archon.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Shabapaduba?&rdquo; Joe Biden questions, gesturing vaguely towards Kaegan with a befuddled expression on his face. &ldquo;I-I coulda sworn, man. That right there is Corn Pop! He&rsquo;s a bad dude, usedta run a buncha bad boys&hellip;&rdquo;</p>
<p>Kaegan throws up his hands. &ldquo;I don&rsquo;t know bro. I ain&rsquo;t named Corn Pop. There are 8 billion people in the world and only one corn pop. I probably ain&rsquo;t him.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Biden grows angry and begins foaming at the mouth. &ldquo;Come on man! You ain&rsquo;t black, you lying, dog - faced pony soldier! You&rsquo;re a Corn Pop &lsquo;cause I says you&rsquo;re a Corn Pop!&rdquo; The politician throws his head back in anger and thrusts forwards his right hand. &ldquo;BIDEN BLAST!&rdquo; he screams in fury, causing a blue pulse of energy to arc between his hand and Kaegan, - reducing the later to a pile of ashes.</p>
<p>&ldquo;No!&rdquo; Screams Hayden. &ldquo;They killed Kaegan!&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;You bastards!&rdquo; I echo.</p>
<p>Fury begins rising in Jack&rsquo;s bosom, fury like he&rsquo;s never felt before. His eyes glow red with wrath - the wrath of the god emperor of mankind. The Earth begins to shake and thunder roles. &ldquo;Lɪsᴛᴇɴ ᴜᴘ, sᴏᴄɪᴀʟɪsᴛ sᴄᴜᴍ!&rdquo; outpours an otherworldly, ferocious voice quite unlike his own. &ldquo;Yᴏᴜ&rsquo;ᴠᴇ ᴋɪʟʟᴇᴅ Kᴇᴀɢᴀɴ, ʙᴜᴛ ʜᴇ ᴡᴀsɴ&rsquo;ᴛ ᴛʜᴇ ꜰɪʀsᴛ! I ᴋɴᴏᴡ ᴛʜᴇ ʜɪsᴛᴏʀʏ ᴏꜰ ʏᴏᴜʀ sᴏᴄɪᴀʟɪsᴍ! I ᴋɴᴏᴡ ᴛʜᴇ ᴡᴏʀᴅs ʏᴏᴜ ᴄᴀɴ&rsquo;ᴛ sᴛᴀɴᴅ ᴛᴏ ʜᴇᴀʀ, ᴛʜᴇ ᴡᴏʀᴅs ᴛʜᴀᴛ ᴇxᴏʀᴄɪsᴇ ᴀɴʏ ʟɪʙᴇʀᴀʟ ғʀᴏᴍ ᴛʜɪs ᴍᴏʀᴛᴀʟ ᴘʟᴀɴᴇ!</p>
<p><em><strong>&ldquo;ɪPʜᴏɴᴇ! &hellip;</strong></em></p>
<p><em><strong>&hellip; Vᴇɴᴇᴢᴜᴇʟᴀ! &hellip;</strong></em></p>
<p><em><strong>&hellip; ONE HUNDRED &hellip;</strong></em></p>
<p><em><strong>&hellip; UNDECILLION &hellip;</strong></em></p>
<p><em><strong>&hellip; DDDEEEAAADDD!!!!&rdquo;</strong></em></p>
<p>The fiends cover their ears, trying to shield themselves from those fateful, ruinous words. But, it is to no avail. They begin screeching in pain, and soon are melting away like the Nazis at the end of <em>Indiana Jones and the Raiders of the Lost Ark.</em></p>
<p>Jack sighs. &ldquo;Another cuck leftist destroyed.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&hellip;</p>
<p>If socialism killed 100 undecillion people, as Jack proved with facts and logic, and there are 8 billion people in the world right now (as Kaegan stated), then how many orders of magnitude more people has socialism killed then are alive today?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-five-parousia">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Thirty-Eight: Tesla Man - Least of the Archons</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/38/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/38/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>At the crack of Philip&rsquo;s whip, Star in the Morning Sky begins lumbering forwards on her borderline defunct legs. As she reaches 8.8 miles per hour, Jack and his company enter the tunnel of light once more. As they go forward, Jack ceases to be the disembodied ghost he has been, and finds himself arrayed as the god - emperor of mankind once more. His triceps swell, he gains the abs of an anime tomboy, and golden armor covers his body.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Wait, something&rsquo;s wrong!&rdquo; Philip declares with manly yet apprehensive perturbance. &ldquo;Earth isn&rsquo;t up ahead! This darned horse is taking us to the moon!&rdquo;</p>
<p>But, before Philip can stop anything, the tunnel of light vanishes, and the carriage grinds to a halt on solid, firmly material ground. Jack closes his eyes, expecting to die like an imposter thrown out of the airlock. But, he doesn&rsquo;t. He breathes in and slowly opens his eyes, finding himself still very much alive.</p>
<p>They step outside the carriage to find themselves in a hideous moon base, made entirely of plastic - exactly like every generic spaceship on TV.</p>
<p>&ldquo;What the hell is going on! Wikipedia doesn&rsquo;t say anything about there being a base like this on the moon!&rdquo; says Jimmy Wales.</p>
<p>A strange, A.I. generated cackling sounds behind them. &ldquo;Ha. Ha. Ha. You are fools.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Jack turns around wildly and draws his sword, but he only sees an expensive - looking Tesla car. But then, its parts begin shifting into a new form - the form of a huge man made of plastic and steel.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Like zoinks! It&rsquo;s a transformer!&rdquo; Shaggy proclaims.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Before my augmentation, I was called Elon Musk, and I am the least of the archons. How dare you trespass on my moon base?&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Wait, this is totally fake!&rdquo; I say. &ldquo;How come no one found this place when people went to the moon? There has to be a naturalistic explanation for this.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;No, no one ever went to the moon. This is where UFOs hail from, and it has been so since the time of the ancient Egyptians. To keep the mortals from discovering them, they were forbidden from coming to the moon.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Just as I am about to respond, Jimmy Wales jumps into action and begins doing battle with Elon Musk - quoting negative statistics about spaceX and Tesla all the while. The fight is long, hard, and brutal. But, in the end, the African American businessman falls to his knees in subjection.</p>
<p>&ldquo;No! You may have defeated me, but you cannot defeat the other archons! You are on the road to destruction! All your base are belong to us! The others are gathered at Jeffry Epstein&rsquo;s island, and they will summon the antichrist in 37 minutes, bringing about the end times. My fastest UFO will get you there in 27 minutes. How long, pray tell, will that leave you to fight them?&rdquo;</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-five-parousia">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
