<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Religion on AlvinMcGee.xyz</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/religion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Religion on AlvinMcGee.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Alvin McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.svg</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Empty or Half Full? Religious people respond.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/religion/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>We also asked people of all faiths and no faith &ndash; God&rsquo;s gotta have something to say about the great questions of life, right?</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>The agnostic says: I don&rsquo;t know.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The strong agnostic says: You don&rsquo;t know.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The gnostic says: I know, and it makes me feel important, so you don&rsquo;t get to know.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The atheist says: &hellip; [excuse us, we appear to have contacted a brick by mistake &ndash; it lacks a belief in God]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Catholic says: I know that her accidents are those a glass, but in essence this object is obviously Natalie Portman. Damn &hellip; she&rsquo;s so hot &hellip; [looks at glass, eyes glaze over, and begins to drool]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The high - church Anglican says: OMG SISTER, you are SO RIGHT!!! SLAY QUEEN!!! [looks at Catholic, eyes glaze over, and begins to drool]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The low - church Anglican says: Nah girlies, that&rsquo;s too far. Like, the glass is def Natalie Portman, but she&rsquo;s just there in spirit or something.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Jew says: Huh? Why do you people think the glass is Natalie Portman?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Southern Baptist says: She isn&rsquo;t!!! They&rsquo;re wrong!!! It just commemorates her!!! Or something!!!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Quaker says: Oh, it might be Natalie Portman, it might not, I don&rsquo;t really care.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>An unnamed Presbyterian says: WHAT&rsquo;S WRONG WITH YOU PEOPLE?! You stand there, claiming that this is but a glass, but you know in your heart that it is Natalie Portman. Everybody out there, despite their claims to the contrary, knows perfectly well that this glass is Natalie Portman. [stands back, inclining his head slightly, admiring his unmatched powers to read minds.]</p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
