<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Math Problems Season 1 on AlvinMcGee.xyz</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/math-problems-season-1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Math Problems Season 1 on AlvinMcGee.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Alvin McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/math-problems-season-1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.svg</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Three: In the Criminal Justice System, Copyright Violations are Considered Especially Heinous</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/3/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>As it happens, one of the games Jack pirated contained a single sprite ripped from a Nintendo game. As soon as Shigeru Miyamoto was made aware of this vicious felony, he dispatched Nintendo&rsquo;s elite legal goons to deal with the young scoundrel. They quickly capture Jack and have him hauled before a grand jury to stand trial for his crimes against God, nature, and humanity.</p>
<p>For every 17.75 people who torrented the game from Jack&rsquo;s website, he will be condemned to spend 48 years inside the ADX Florence Supermax Detention Center. If 18,427 people torrented the game from Jack&rsquo;s site, how many years will he be sentenced to spend in ADX Florence? If the average lifespan of an American male is 74.5 years, how many lifetimes will Jack be condemned to in ADX Florence?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-one-the-tale-of-a-wayward-jack">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem Two: Piracy is not a Victimless Crime</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/2/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack opens a site for pirating video games. After a game comes out, it takes Jack five hours to crack the game and three hours to load the necessary ransomware onto it. If Jack pirates five games a week and will get a thousand dollars from every piece of ransomeware someone downloads, how many dollars will he make an in one week if six people download games from his site every hour?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems/#season-one-the-tale-of-a-wayward-jack">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Problem One: Humble Beginnings</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/math/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/math/1/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack steals his mother&rsquo;s wedding ring and auctions it on eBay to pay for his heroin addiction. Every five minutes, the taking price goes up by 100 dollars. If this goes on for two and a half hours, how much money will Jack get? If Jack can buy a gram of heroin for 120 dollars, and he consumes five grams of heroin every day, how long will be be able to maintain his drug addiction?</p>
<p><a href="/humor/problems//#season-one-the-tale-of-a-wayward-jack">&lt;== Back to Math Problems Home Page &lt;==</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
