<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Half Empty or Half Full? on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/half-empty-or-half-full/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Half Empty or Half Full? on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>David McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/half-empty-or-half-full/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.png</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Empty or Half Full? Philosophers respond.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/phil/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/phil/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In our quest to find out whether the glass was half empty or half full, we first asked the world&rsquo;s great philosophers. Here are their responses.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Leibniz says: This is the fullest of all possible glasses.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Schopenhauer says: Everything sucks, including the glass.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Thales says: The glass is completely full because the air in the top half is also water.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The mereological nihilist says: There is no glass.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Aristotle says: The glass is actually half empty but possesses the potentiality to be half full.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Anselm says: In using this vessel as part of thine shitty comedy operation, thou hast offended its unfathomably great honor. (<em>sighs</em>) Looks like we&rsquo;re gonna have to set you on fire, bud.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The logical positivist says: Your question is not only extremely annoying but also utterly meaningless.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The panpsychist says: Why don&rsquo;t you just ask him, man?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Plato says: The glass halfway participates in the form of fullness.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Spinoza says: On God or nature, you brought me back to life just to ask me that?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The phenomenal conservative says: It seem totally obvious that it&rsquo;s half full.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The solipsist says: The glass doesn&rsquo;t exist and neither do you. Oh, you disagree with that? That&rsquo;s just what a nonexistent person would say.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The analytic philosopher says: Okay, let&rsquo;s unpack this a little &hellip; [begins a seven hour monologue discussing the precise usage of the terms involved and their history, making heavy use of symbolic logic and Bayes&rsquo; Theorem all the while. His conclusion: &ldquo;I dunno bro, it&rsquo;s probably just semantics or something.&rdquo;]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The continental philosopher says: Hark upon the serendipitous quintessence with which we must cogitate upon such a query - multitudinous intrepid spirits hath ruminated upon this antique problem passim the eons; for the portion of this individuated subjectivity, think he that the chalice mays perchance be halfway empty - if considered from a certain point of view, but that, in pure disreflective beingness - if perchance such a thing might there be - the query musts finally remain unanswered; or perhaps there is no that such to be gobbledegooked; perchance instead it be that gobbledebooking shall not maintain apace of the clandestine ruminations liken to &hellip; [he continues on like this for the next fifteen minutes, liberally using many obscure words and several he just made up (as well as all punctuation marks save periods). One of our interns gets the best sleep of her life. Towards the end he begins shouting in French, throws the glass out the window, and faints]</p>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<p>Some other people wandered in and wanted to tell us what about the glass. We kind of felt sorry for them, so we wrote down their answers too.</p>
<p>Our intern sighs and asks &ldquo;Okay, y&rsquo;all think the glass is half empty?&rdquo;</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Jordan Peterson responds: [chuckles] I&rsquo;m terrified that it might be, how&rsquo;s that? &hellip; Y&rsquo;know, Bucko, you use words like &ldquo;full&rdquo; and &ldquo;empty,&rdquo; just assuming we know what they mean, but we don&rsquo;t. Fullness, it&rsquo;s like, it&rsquo;s what makes you get out of bed in the morning &ndash; I know you aren&rsquo;t full, I&rsquo;m bloody well not. None of us are really full. We&rsquo;re all at least a little empty (that was Nietzsche&rsquo;s core insight). If the glass isn&rsquo;t full then it&rsquo;s like we have no set point in our hierarchy of values! And then, like, how are you gonna do anything at all?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>R.C. Sproul says: WHAT&rsquo;S WRONG WITH YOU PEOPLE!?!?!?!? You just keep standing there, calling this thing a glass, but you know perfectly well that it&rsquo;s a hip flask. Everyone out there, despite their protestations to the contrary, knows that this is a hip flask. There are no glass - believers, only hip - flask haters and liars. [steps back, looks at our intern very intensely, basks in his own eloquence and moral superiority]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>An Instagram commenter says: The GLASS is the HYPRONIC frequency!! You KEEP trying to MEASURE the GLASS. EAT SHIT AND DIE!! Tt has QUINTESSENCE INNUMERABLE!! Praise YESHUA!!</p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Empty or Half Full? Politicans respond.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/politics/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>For good measure, we also reached out to several prominent politicians for their thoughts on the matter.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Donald Trump says: Half of this glass was stolen by brutal MS - 13 gang members, allowed to invade across our Southern border by the radical left &ndash; I&rsquo;m telling you, it&rsquo;s true. It&rsquo;s just horrible, horrible what they&rsquo;ve done to our country.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Joe Biden says: what you saying, Jack? &hellip; &ldquo;shabapaqoba?&rdquo; &hellip; Come on, man.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Kamala Harris says: Hehe &ndash; it&rsquo;s in the Venn diagram of glasses which are half empty and glasses which are half full &ndash; hehe.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Marjorie Taylor Green says: THE JEWS STOLE HALF OF THE GLASS WITH THEIR WEATHER MACHINES!! IT IS WRITTEN ON THE GUIDESTONES!!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Beto O&rsquo;Rourke says: [something obscene about cows. We daren&rsquo;t repeat it here]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Kristie Noem says: I shot the glass.</p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Empty or Half Full? Religious people respond.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/religion/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In our quest to figure out whether the glass is half empty or half full, we interviewed several people of all faiths and no faith &ndash; God&rsquo;s gotta have something to say about the great questions of life, right?</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>The agnostic says: I don&rsquo;t know.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The strong agnostic says: You don&rsquo;t know.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The gnostic says: I know, and it makes me feel important, so you don&rsquo;t get to know.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The atheist says: &hellip; [excuse us, we appear to have contacted a brick by mistake &ndash; it lacks a belief in God]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Catholic says: I know that her accidents are those a glass, but in essence this object is obviously Natalie Portman. Damn &hellip; she&rsquo;s so hot &hellip; [looks at glass, eyes glaze over, and begins to drool]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The high - church Anglican says: OMG SISTER, you are SO RIGHT!!! SLAY QUEEN!!! [looks at Catholic, eyes glaze over, and begins to drool]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The low - church Anglican says: Nah girlies, that&rsquo;s too far. Like, the glass is def Natalie Portman, but she&rsquo;s just there in spirit or something.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Jew says: Huh? Why do you people think the glass is Natalie Portman?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Southern Baptist says: She isn&rsquo;t!!! They&rsquo;re wrong!!! It just commemorates her!!! Or something!!!</p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Empty or Half Full?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/glass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 10:00:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/glass/glass/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Whether the glass is half empty or half full is and has always been a matter of much debate. In a question to answer this age - old question, we first asked the world&rsquo;s philosophers, then we asked members of various religions. And,for good measure, we asked several major political figures.</p>
<p><a href="/humor/glass/phil">Part I: Philosophers</a></p>
<p><a href="/humor/glass/religion">Part II: Religions</a></p>
<p><a href="/humor/glass/politics">Part III: Politicans</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
