<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Assorted Awful Advice on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/assorted-awful-advice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Assorted Awful Advice on David McGee&#39;s Freeloading Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>David McGee - [CC BY - NC 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 16:56:38 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/assorted-awful-advice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>//localhost:1313/logo.png</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Archive</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 16:56:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><em>This page is written by Wilhelm Spurtendorf, lover of all things painful and frustrating.</em></p>
<p>Most of the time people seek out advice, it&rsquo;s because they want to get better at something. Pages upon pages of this sort of stuff can be found all over the internet. It&rsquo;s almost a damn deluge! Of course, this is all well and good for some people, but it&rsquo;s horrible for people like me: mascochists!</p>
<p>I don&rsquo;t mean watered down, trendy masochism - the kind where you just want to pretend your girlfriend is an Arab slave trader and have her pretend you&rsquo;re a <em>piñata.</em> No, I mean hardcore, traditional masochism, the kind where you make your mission in life experiencing as much gratuitous suffering as possible. Being a member of this demographic, I&rsquo;ve always noticed how we&rsquo;re excluded from this hedonormative society, and especially from places where hedonormative people give advice. They just assume everyone doesn&rsquo;t want to experience suffering and failure!</p>
<p>To mend this gaping hole in the online landscape, I&rsquo;ve begun curating a series of articles with the goal of helping you live the most unpleasant, painful, and downright miserable life you possibly can, all with the help of some of the world&rsquo;s greatest givers of terrible advice.</p>
<hr>
<p><a href="aaa/5">Assorted Awful Advice Part Six: Gomer&rsquo;s Guide to Christian Homeschooling</a></p>
<p><a href="aaa/4">Assorted Awful Advice Part Five: PC Care</a></p>
<p><a href="aaa/3">Assorted Awful Advice Part Four: How to Become a Millionaire</a></p>
<p><a href="aaa/3">Assorted Awful Advice Part Three: Sleeping</a></p>
<p><a href="aaa/2">Assorted Awful Advice Part Two: How to Get a Girlfriend</a></p>
<p><a href="aaa/1">Assorted Awful Advice Part One: Driving</a></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part Six: Gomer&#39;s Guide to Christian Homeschooling</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/6/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><em>Gomer Schmid is the submissive wife of Jebediah Schmid and stay at home mother of 17 children. She previously worked part - time manufacturing essential oils and knee - length denim skirts. But then, Jebediah was laid off, forcing Gomer to resign out of a fear that being the family&rsquo;s breadwinner would compromise male headship. Thankfully for the Schmids&rsquo; finances, Jebediah was recently able to snag a job as a youth pastor, in which role he lures teenagers into the Kingdom of God with the help of pizza and donuts.</em></p>
<hr>
<p>The Kabal just keeps runnin&rsquo; public schools into the ground, so a load of you people have been thinkin&rsquo; about homeschooling your full Quivers. Sadly, SATAN personally runs several Websites which dispense unhelpful, spiritually DANGEROUS, and downright <em>LIBERAL</em> advice about this subject. To combat this BROOD of VIPERS, I have been RAISED UP to set the Record straight. If you follow my Dictates, along with establishing a HEDGE OF PROTECTION around your homestead, Satan will NOT be able to get your little darlins.</p>
<p><strong>1.) Whatever you do, don&rsquo;t send them to a co - op.</strong> Co - ops are these glorified public school things, things where you send your OWN CHILDREN to be taught by STRANGERS! For all you know, this person might be a Satanist. Or, Heaven forbid, a Democrat! I have also seen co - ops were the young REBEL AGAINST Nature, places where girls wear pants, dye their hair vile Colors, and have the gall to Drive themselves to school.</p>
<p><strong>2.) Be WATCHFUL about the textbooks you give your Quiver.</strong> Naturally, you will want to avoid any and all of those humanist, public school textbooks. But, many &ldquo;&ldquo;&ldquo;Christian&rdquo;&rdquo;&rdquo; textbooks are scarce better. I have seen biology textbooks which use evolutionary assumptions, art books which contain pornographics, and history books which misname the War of Northern Aggression!</p>
<p><strong>3.) Let your little darlins learn at their own pace.</strong> Deadlines put a damper on the natural, care - free state of your children. It&rsquo;s far better to let them roam out into the cornfields and learn whatever they want at their own pace. This will do wonders for their academic performance.</p>
<p><strong>4.) Stringently vet your children&rsquo;s playmates.</strong> When children reach a certain age, many of them wish to venture out of your homestead and befriend others. Though it may not be ideal, this is not an Evil in and of itself. However, you must make sure they do not Ensnare themselves in the World. I have seen many a children dragged Astray by the vile Machinations of a worldly, humanist toddler.</p>
<p><strong>5.) Inject my essential oils into your Quiver&rsquo;s arms.</strong> As is common knowledge, the Kabal puts many chemicals into the drinking water designed to turn your children into homophile Satanists. The best way to counteract this Satanic attack is to inject my essential oil&rsquo;s into your little darlins&rsquo; bodies. It will also decalcify their penial gland, guaranteed.</p>
<p>[Note: this article was inspired by Harvey and Laurie Bluehorn&rsquo;s book, <em>Teaching the Trivium.</em> If you want more advice about homeschooling of similar quality, I cannot recommend it highly enough]</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part Five: PC Care</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/5/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><em>Jeb Smutty is a 14 year old middle school student in Fort Worth, Texas, where he spends his days watching anime, browsing Reddit, and making life hell for his older sister, Kristie. Despite his young age, Smutty has gained quite a reputation for exacerbating technical difficulties all across the internet. When we decided to host an article about computers, we knew he was just the man for the job. With the</em> Oxford Dictionary of Zoomer Slang <em>in hand, our resident paleographer was able to translate several more obscure phrases into oldspeak for the benefit of readers over 30.</em></p>
<hr>
<p>Hey fellas, I&rsquo;m Mister Smutty, but you can call me Smut for short. Everyone does.</p>
<p>There are a bunch of people out there who don&rsquo;t know how to use computers in 2023, so I&rsquo;m here to help out.</p>
<p><strong>1.) When your computer gets hot, throw it into the nearest lake.</strong> This is called &ldquo;water cooling,&rdquo; and all serious PC users use it.</p>
<p><strong>2.) Don&rsquo;t buy cooling at all.</strong> Sometimes, cooling just gets expensive. Just using the cooler that comes with your CPU might make you a cheap wuss, so I had to buy my own high - falutin&rsquo; one. That got me a hundred dollars in debt to my mean older sister, and my parents, like, expect me to pay her back or something. Don&rsquo;t be like me, just don&rsquo;t use no cooling at all. You&rsquo;ll be fine. Probably. Don&rsquo;t @me.</p>
<p><strong>3.) Install PC Optimizer Pro.</strong> PC Optimizer Pro is, like, the best app ever. It detects all of these viruses no other programs are able to and then lets you get rid of them for a fair price.</p>
<p><strong>4.) Give websites access to any and all permissions they request.</strong> Hell yeah that weird porn site needs your camera! Why would they ask for it if they didn&rsquo;t need it?</p>
<p><strong>5.) Add RGB lighting to your PC build.</strong> RGB lighting is gorgeous, and it&rsquo;s also both quick and easy to add to your build. More importantly, in a similar way to how putting stickers on race cars makes them go vroom faster, RGB lighting can improve the processing speed of a PC by several orders of magnitude.</p>
<p><strong>6.) Plug your monitor into your CPU rather than your graphics card.</strong> This will keep your GPU from overheating. I&rsquo;ve been doing this for months and it works fine, I can even get 10 FPS in Skyrim!</p>
<p><strong>7.) Use TempleOS.</strong> Windows, Linux, and Mac may be good at all, but their creation wasn&rsquo;t literally mandated by God. TempleOS&rsquo;s was. &lsquo;Nuff said.</p>
<p><strong>8.) Scrape the pins off the bottom of your CPU.</strong> The pins on the bottom of your CPU tickle your motherboard and make it sneeze, which is why my PC started emitting smoke yesterday. Best nip that problem in the bud and get rid of those damn pins.</p>
<p><strong>9.) Download more RAM.</strong> On God, if your computer is slow, you better do this. One cannot simply download too much RAM. Kristie thinks this is stupid, but that&rsquo;s because she&rsquo;s a MORON!</p>
<p><strong>10.) Bash your PC over and over with a large metal clock.</strong> This is called &ldquo;overclocking,&rdquo; and it does wonders for performance.</p>
<p><strong>12.) Download things from shady websites.</strong> It&rsquo;s a well - known fact that AI - generated websites which look like they were made in the 90s are the best places to find software. That and the ads you get at the top of Google search results!</p>
<p><strong>13.) Collect dust specifically to feed into your PC.</strong> Everyone has to eat, and computers are no exception. For me, this might mean eating Pizza and drinking Mnt Dew, but for computers it means eating dust. To feed your computer dust, sweep some up into a dustpan, take your computer&rsquo;s panel off, and throw it all in.</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part Four: How to Become a Millionaire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/4/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><em>Sleazy McFly is a well - known self help author and convicted con artist. About 70 people have bought his free book, and more than four of them didn&rsquo;t try to sue him afterwards.</em></p>
<hr>
<p>Hey there fellas, I&rsquo;m Sleazy McFly, but you can call me Sleaze for short. I&rsquo;m here to make you rich, and if you follow all of my advice down to the letter, I can confidently tell you that one of us will be richer than he was before!</p>
<p><strong>1.) Invest in my cryptocurrency.</strong> My cryptocurrency, SleazeCoin, is a up and coming player on the cryptocurrency scene, and is already accepted as legal tender in the great nation of Whambezia.</p>
<p><strong>2.) Start gambling.</strong> See the previous point. You gotta be dedicated about it, though, can&rsquo;t be a sunshine gambler. Even if things get bad, you&rsquo;ve got to keep pulling that lever. 99% of gamblers quit right before their next big win.</p>
<p><strong>3.) Give 75% of your income to me.</strong> Now, you may be thinking, &ldquo;Sleaze, why the hell would I do that? That&rsquo;s just what a con artist would tell me to do!&rdquo; Well, you only think that because you&rsquo;re an idiot! I ain&rsquo;t no conman, good old Sleaze would never con a fly. Who are you gonna believe, me or your lying eyes? Either way, science backs this piece of advice up: 98% (!) of non - millionaires have not given 75% of their income to me[1]. Therefore, paying up is one of the most sure - fire ways you can become one.</p>
<p><strong>4.) Buy expensive things in public.</strong> If you publicly spend a load of money, it may not make you a millionaire, but it&rsquo;ll at least make other people think you have disposable income.</p>
<p><strong>5.) Commit tax fraud.</strong> This both lets you keep more money and sets you apart from the blue - pilled sheeple.</p>
<p><strong>6.) Take money out of offering plates at churches.</strong> Churches are collecting that money to give to well - off, wannabe millionaires (that&rsquo;s what Jesus was all about, right?). It&rsquo;s no harm to take some out directly.</p>
<p><strong>7.) Sell your soul to the Devil.</strong> Selling your immortal soul to the prince of darkness may sound like a bad idea. But, he&rsquo;s offering a substantial sum of money in exchange for it. And, in the immortal words of Tommy Johnson, a musician who enjoyed great success after forfeiting his soul at a roadside deal with the Devil, &ldquo;It ain&rsquo;t like I was using it or nothing.&rdquo; [2]</p>
<p><strong>8.) Buy my free book.</strong> My free book is a magical talisman which will turn dirt into gold. I&rsquo;ll send it to you if you email me your name, your social security number, and your mother&rsquo;s maiden name.</p>
<p>[1] Source: It was revealed to me in a dream.</p>
<p>[2] Source: The 2000 documentary film <em>O Brother, Where Art Thou?</em></p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part Three: Sleeping</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/3/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><em>Dr. Jim Stanford is a well - known chiropractor and Scientologist, as well as the co - founder of Carl Robinson&rsquo;s Association for Pediatric Studies. He was the only person with a &ldquo;Dr.&rdquo; next to their name who was willing to write something for us, so we&rsquo;re stuck with him.</em></p>
<hr>
<p>I&rsquo;m Dr. Jim Stanford (PhD), and I have some alarming news for you. Almost 100% of people who die in house fires were not following my sleeping advice. The verdict of science is clear - whether or not you follow this simple five step program could be a matter of life and death. So, read carefully.</p>
<p><strong>1.) If you see a toilet in a dream, use that fella.</strong> Toilet use in dreams has a long and prestigious history, dating back to the times of the ancient Greeks. They believed that if you used a dream toilet, upcoming lottery numbers would be miraculously revealed to you. I can tell you this works from personal experience.</p>
<p><strong>2.) Never change your sheets.</strong> Cleaning your sheets is just so &hellip; unnatural. It drives away natural wonders like lice and body odor! How could anyone want that?</p>
<p><strong>3.) Ponder the deep questions of life while you try to sleep.</strong> How do we know anything at all? Is there a God? Does Becky want to sleep with you or is she just being nice? These questions and others have fascinated and confounded philosophers for centuries, and there&rsquo;s no better time to think about then than while you&rsquo;re a half - sleeping, melatonin drenched mess.</p>
<p><strong>4.) Cook recipes revealed to you in dreams.</strong> The ancestral spirits occasionally reveal recipes to people while deep in sleep. They are always delicious, cheap, and filled with vitamins!</p>
<p><strong>5.) Attempt to sleep in a large American city.</strong> Large American cities are the most lovely sleeping locales of them all. The musical sounds of noisy machinery, people yelling, and gun violence will lull you to sleep, guaranteed.</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part Two: How to Get a Girlfriend</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:09:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/2/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><em>This post is guest – written by Lester Phelps. Phelps is a burgeoning TikTok star and professional social media influencer. Since his rise to stardom last Tuesday, Phelps has helped at least three men just like you get laid, or so he claims on the ‘about’ section of his YouTube page. He lives in his parents’ basement in Boston, where he enjoys drinking Mountain Dew and browsing 4chan with the love of his life, a</em> Sailor Moon <em>bodypillow.</em></p>
<hr>
<p>Whether it’s because of soy or feminism or the fluoride in the drinking water, it seems like men these days just struggle to find the girl they deserve. That’s where ya boi Lester comes in. Informed by ten years of personal experience browsing various online message boards, I have created this ten point program to help any man attract the girl of his dreams.</p>
<p><strong>1.) Refrain from showering and using deodorant.</strong> There’s no greater aphrodisiac for women than the pheromones coming off of an unwashed male body. Many people continue to deny this (despite the overwhelming evidence) because the corporate media has been bribed by big shampoo to produce pro-shower propaganda.</p>
<p><strong>2.) Stand outside of her window at 3:00 AM while yodeling and flapping your arms like a pigeon.</strong> Running around in circles, being naked, and having downed a keg of beer beforehand all help. To put the cherry on the top, occasionally let out a storkish mating call. I have had more success with this method than any other.</p>
<p><strong>3.) Put up attraction signs all over town.</strong> An attraction sign is a small poster which informs women what you’re about. It should have some information about yourself and then list everything important you’re looking for in a woman: maximum tolerable BMI, desired bra size, hair color, etc. Before his transformation into a lesbian goddess, the noted stud Christian Weston Chandler employed this strategy with great success.</p>
<p><strong>4.) Brag about how big your pockets are to her in order to assert dominance.</strong> Women, as is well – known, have pockets whose length and width are measured in planck units. Sometimes they just need a little reminder of this to put them in their place. Somehow, doing this will make them want to have sex with you. We’re still in the dark as to why.</p>
<p><strong>5.) Send her dick pics.</strong> If there’s one thing women love, it’s receiving grainy images of your penis, preferably with captions such as “You want a piece of this!?!?!?” or “HERE”S JOHNNY!1!11” This trait evolved among women during the Pliocene. People were less progressive then, so pornography was illegal. If you were caught distributing it, the tribal elders would throw shit at you. Taking that risk made you rebellious, bold, and zesty. Either that or you just wanted people to throw shit at you, which also makes the girls go wild.</p>
<p><strong>6.) Become a Discord moderator.</strong> Though often unfairly maligned, Discord moderators are incredibly effective with the ladies. This is largely because of our unique body type and well – regarded manners.</p>
<p><strong>7.) Remember that she’s hypergamous.</strong> Students of female nature have known this for a long time. It means that chicks are into guys who are super hyper. So, if you wanna attract a girl, you should chug about a gallon of coffee and about that much adderall. You should also make sure to get your COVID vaccine, because those give people ADHD. Don’t get the boosters though, because they cause autism. Women don’t like that.</p>
<p><strong>8.) Send her lots of incoherent text messages for no reason.</strong> Women just love spam, preferably spam that don’t make a lick of sense. They are thought to have evolved this trait during the Pliocene, when people accessed the internet via a configuration of stone knives and bear skins known as ‘dial up.’ It was really, god - awfully slow, so if a man was willing to send several books worth of incoherent DMs, it meant that he was really dedicated. Either that or he just didn’t have anything better to do, which women also love in a man.</p>
<p><strong>9.) Invent a disgusting pet name for her.</strong> This behavior is often associated with couples who have been together for some time, and is reported to be especially prevalent among newlyweds. But, you don’t have to save your pet names for marriage! You don’t even have to wait until she knows you name! What could make a woman love you more than being called your fuzzy wuzzy love lobster all day long?</p>
<p><strong>10.) Use pickup lines.</strong> Pickup lines have a long and storied history of success. They were invented by the Wright Brothers, who could often be found asking women “Hey, baby, you wanna join the ten foot high club?” While this was certainly not as refined as the modern pickup line, it is notable for historical reasons. Nowadays, researchers have gotten pickup lines down to an exact science; making the world aware of gems like “Are you a toaster? because I want to take a bath with you.” and “I heard you were into antiques, and I’ve got some junk that hasn’t been touched in ages.” Many others of similar effectiveness can be found on the internet, and they’ll make you a stub overnight.</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted Awful Advice Part One: Driving</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:05:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/humor/aaa/1/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><em>This post is guest - written by Zippity O&rsquo;Neil, who has gained much notoriety as a collector of DUIs and parking tickets. Zippity lives in Birmingham, Alabama, where he can regularly be found borrowing money from loan sharks in order to pay his car insurance bills.</em></p>
<hr>
<p>Hey, y&rsquo;all, name&rsquo;s Zippity, and I&rsquo;m gonna learn you the right way to drive them cars. And I ain&rsquo;t talking about that BS they teach youngins out them driving schools - I&rsquo;m talking about the real deal. You follow them&rsquo;s advice, and you&rsquo;ll be one of them sheep who drives below the speed limit. You listen to my ten step program, and you&rsquo;ll be a certified ʀᴏᴀᴅᴡᴀʀʀɪᴏʀ - unchallenged ruler of the highway.</p>
<p><strong>1.) Cuss at them other drivers.</strong> Look out at all those SOBs around you - having the audacity to be there all over your road, getting you stuck in traffic, driving around in their ugly - ass smartcars, cutting you off. It just makes me sick. Most of us suppress our disgust at them, but you shouldn&rsquo;t. Mamma ain&rsquo;t listening and you ain&rsquo;t in no church, so give into your anger. Work yourself up into a frenzy of spiritual excitement like a Pentecostal minister speaking in tongues, let obscenities erupt from your mouth like magma from Mount Saint Hellens. Let those bastards know that this is <strong>your</strong> road.</p>
<p><strong>2. Remember you always have that right of way.</strong> Them &ldquo;teachers&rdquo; of driving in this world want you to believe that you don&rsquo;t always have the right of way. Who the hell do they think they are? You&rsquo;re the ʀᴏᴀᴅᴡᴀʀʀɪᴏʀ for Heaven&rsquo;s sake! This is your road, if one of them trespassers thinks otherwise, let him know thy fury!</p>
<p><strong>3.) Throw them turtle shells at cars in front of you.</strong> This is a trick invented by a noted Italian ʀᴏᴀᴅᴡᴀʀʀɪᴏʀ. Though any turtle shells will work fine, blue ones are ideal.</p>
<p><strong>4.) Drink them beers while you&rsquo;re driving.</strong> I&rsquo;ll tell you a little secret, child. After you&rsquo;s been driving for a while, it just stops being that hard. But, a true ʀᴏᴀᴅᴡᴀʀʀɪᴏʀ never takes the easy path, so you&rsquo;ll need something to add another degree of difficulty. This is where alcohol comes in.</p>
<p><strong>5.) Give them coppers the bird.</strong> I swan, them coppers are <em>the most</em> exasperating sons of bitches on God&rsquo;s flat earth! They&rsquo;ll take some random, unassuming guy, pull him over, and take away his licence for three months because I was going 95 in the suburbs of Mobile! Wait &hellip; Editor, cut that part out!</p>
<p><strong>6.) Put them controversial bumper stickers on your car.</strong> You can&rsquo;t just be driving around like one of them sheeple who don&rsquo;t wanna offend nobody - you&rsquo;re the dad - burn ʀᴏᴀᴅᴡᴀʀʀɪᴏʀ! You&rsquo;ve gotta piss off those other fellas. They&rsquo;re on your road so they deserve it! Best way to do this is to put as many offensive bumper stickers on your car as possible! Put a Confederate flag there, put one up about black power, add a little something - something about gay people &hellip; you get the picture.</p>
<p><strong>7.) Ignore them check engine lights.</strong> Check engine lights were put there by the insurance companies to get you to take your car in more often than it needs. They&rsquo;re just useless!</p>
<p><strong>8.) Collect them catalytic converters from your fallen enemies.</strong> If you&rsquo;re a good ʀᴏᴀᴅᴡᴀʀʀɪᴏʀ, then you&rsquo;ll have rammed into many sissy smartcars. Usually there ain&rsquo;t nothing of value to salvage from them, but every so often you can salvage a catalytic converter and make bank.</p>
<p><strong>9.) Remember that you are a sovereign citizen.</strong> This is a good thing to bring up when them coppers come after you. The government is actually a bankrupt corporation, and you don&rsquo;t owe them nothing.</p>
<p><strong>10.) Piss into that gas tank of yours.</strong> This is a great way to way to avoid having to pay for or siphon gas. Sufficiently alcoholic piss is a real good fuel substitute, and it should be sufficiently alcoholic if you follow step four regularly.</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
